<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[RBC: Banking Advisor]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://rbc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/RBCEARLYTALENT1/job/106-BEAUREPAIRE-DRBEACONSFIELD/Banking-Advisor_R-0000086335-3?q=2024&Category=7911130ac480011864965493391d0000&Category=7911130ac480011864964fc0692d0000&Category=7911130ac480011864965833370e0002&Sub_Category=7911130ac48001186377883e518d0000&Sub_Category=7911130ac480011863776c9b15830004&Sub_Category=7911130ac480011863776e6878250003&Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&Country=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>106 BEAUREPAIRE DR:BEACONSFIELD<br>3131 BOUL DE LA CÔTE VERTU:MONTRÉAL<br>610 BOUL ST JEAN:POINTE-CLAIRE<br>101 BOUL CARDINAL LÉGER:PINCOURT<br>3610 BOUL ST JEAN:DOLLARD-DES ORMEAUX<br>View All 9 Locations<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>R-0000086335<br>Job Description<br>**This is an opportunity for candidates to express their interest in current and future positions in the West-Island of Montreal locations**<br>What is the opportunity?<br>This unique position calls on your client-focused sales expertise and natural problem-solving skills to maximize each client interaction. Specifically, you help clients with their everyday banking, credit, and investment needs. As an RBC ambassador, you add value in the moments that matter most to clients and collaborate with RBC partners to help clients achieve their goals. Whether you’re demonstrating to a client how to use digital banking, on-boarding a new client, or referring a complex opportunity to a specialist, your expertise will contribute to creating meaningful and memorable client experiences to drive client satisfaction and loyalty.<br>What will you do?<br>Proactively engage with clients in all areas of the branch and in the community, uncovering banking needs, providing help and advice, as well as identifying sales and referral opportunities<br>Focus on client education and demonstration, leveraging technology to deliver a memorable client experience, drive sales, and retain business<br>Respond to client-initiated contact, assisting them with a full range of financial transactions<br>Actively listen and engage clients in conversation to further understand their individual needs<br>Proactively take ownership of resolving and preventing client banking problems<br>Cultivate and maintain relationships with partners to make the most of business opportunities and referrals<br>What do you need to succeed?<br>Must-have<br>Mutual Funds accreditation, or willingness to obtain it (i.e., Investment Funds in Canada or the Canadian Securities Course)<br>Demonstrated passion for putting clients first, as well as success in a hands-on, target-driven sales environment<br>Problem-solving and people skills, with the ability to build strong relationships and proactively connect with clients<br>Flexibility, eagerness to learn, strong personal ethics, and a hunger for success<br>Digital literacy across a broad range of devices (i.e., smartphones, tablets, laptops, etc.)<br>Bilingualism (English and French) required, as you will regularly serve our clients with English and French-speaking needs.<br>Nice-to-have<br>Track record in building rapport and maintaining client relationships within the financial or service industry.<br>What are the advantages for you?<br>We strive to meet the challenge of being our best mind, a progressive mindset to continue to grow and work together to provide trusted advice to help our clients thrive and thrive in communities. We care about each other, realize our potential, make a difference for our communities, and achieve mutual success.<br>Network and develop lasting relationships with students from diverse backgrounds across Canada<br>Participate in fun events and gamification challenges to help you build your career toolkit while enjoying a work-life balance.<br>Leaders who support your development with coaching and learning opportunities<br>Work in a dynamic, collaborative, progressive and high-performance team<br>Ability to make a difference and lasting impact<br>Enjoy a comfortable work environment with the ability to dress casually<br>Job Skills<br>Advice Based Solutions, Client Centricity, Client Discovery, Communication, Critical Thinking, Curiosity, Data Analysis, Digital Literacy<br>Additional Job Details<br>Address:<br>316 AV DORVAL:DORVAL<br>City:<br>Dorval<br>Country:<br>Canada<br>Work hours/week:<br>37.5<br>Employment Type:<br>Full time<br>Platform:<br>PERSONAL & COMMERCIAL BANKING<br>Job Type:<br>Regular<br>Pay Type:<br>Salaried<br>Posted Date:<br>2024-04-24<br>Application Deadline:<br>2025-12-31<br>Note: Applications will be accepted until 11:59 PM on the day prior to the application deadline date above<br>Inclusion and Equal Opportunity Employment<br>At RBC, we believe an inclusive workplace that has diverse perspectives is core to our continued growth as one of the largest and most successful banks in the world. Maintaining a workplace where our employees feel supported to perform at their best, effectively collaborate, drive innovation, and grow professionally helps to bring our Purpose to life and create value for our clients and communities. RBC strives to deliver this through policies and programs intended to foster a workplace based on respect, belonging and opportunity for all.<br>Join our Talent Community<br><br>Stay in-the-know about great career opportunities at RBC. Sign up and get customized info on our latest jobs, career tips and Recruitment events that matter to you.<br><br>Expand your limits and create a new future together at RBC. Find out how we use our passion and drive to enhance the well-being of our clients and communities at jobs.rbc.com.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIBC: CBAP Commercial Banking Associate (New Grad only)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://cibc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/campus/job/Fort-Saint-John-BC/CBAP-Commercial-Banking-Associate--New-Grad-only-_2520816?Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Fort Saint John, BC<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 17, 2025 (27 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>2520816<br>We’re building a relationship-oriented bank for the modern world. We need talented, passionate professionals who are dedicated to doing what’s right for our clients.<br>At CIBC, we embrace your strengths and your ambitions, so you are empowered at work. Our team members have what they need to make a meaningful impact and are truly valued for who they are and what they contribute.<br>To learn more about CIBC, please visit CIBC.com<br>What you'll be doing  <br>When you become a Commercial Banking Associate, you will be joining a team that for more than a century has been helping businesses reach their full potential. Through a structured and comprehensive training program that includes classroom and on-the-job training, you will have the opportunity to learn how to deliver flexible business solutions and provide dedicated and timely business expertise to help clients realize their goals.   <br>The Commercial Banking team supports our account teams through client acquisition, relationship management as well as transactional support for client-specific financing solutions. As an associate on the team, you will have an opportunity to learn the products, processes, networks and functions to enable and equip you to eventually progress to the Relationship Manager role and oversee your own portfolio of clients.  <br>As a Commercial Banking Associate, you will be assisting our Commercial Banking Managers with their existing clients relationships as well as new financing transactions by providing quality financial and industry analysis as part of the deal team.  You will also participate in all activities through the sales cycle in order to prepare you for the Relationship Manager role. You’ll have a chance to assist with business development initiatives with a focus on meeting growth targets. This means that you will work in identifying business opportunities and financing solutions to meet the needs of the client.  <br>You’ll begin your journey with Orientation Activities to help you get acclimated to the team and role and will equip you with the skills and knowledge to provide the best possible experience to CIBC clients – we know there’s a learning curve and we’re here to help.  <br>It’s hands-on, so you’ll get the real-life experience you need to rise to the challenge.  <br>As an Associate you'll complete a number of training sessions related directly to the role including credit structuring, risk assessment, and cash management. You will have ongoing coaching and mentoring by your leaders and will be supported by a Program Manager who will lead virtual learning sessions, host touchpoints and guide Associates through this structured program.  <br>You’ll have an opportunity to develop a number of soft skills including business development, negotiation and networking.  <br>Important information: .  <br>You must be in your final year of post-secondary education pursuing a degree/diploma in Business, Finance, Accounting, or related fields with an expected graduation date of May 31st, 2026.  <br>Applications should include your resume (no more than 2 pages) and cover letter (no more than 1 page) and academic transcript uploaded as 1 document to the “Resume/CV section” of the application  <br>Work location: Exact city of work location will be confirmed later during the interview process taking into account the selected candidates’ preference. Mobility is an asset.  The primary location is Fort St John, BC but candidates will be considered from surrounding areas including Dawson Creek and Prince George.<br> At CIBC we enable the work environment most optimal for you to thrive in your role. This role will be in office with the occasional off-site meetings with clients. <br>Salary Range for this role is $65,000 - $70,000 <br> How you'll succeed  <br>Client Engagement - Connect on a personal level to make every interaction meaningful. Enhance relationships by collaborating with your team and providing administrative support to ensure client needs are met. Respond to requests by answering questions and providing an exceptional experience.  <br>Relationship Building - Heighten CIBC brand awareness in your community by attending local events and participating in marketing and outreach activities. Grow your network to create lasting connections that will generate future opportunities. Work closely with your team to connect clients with the right opportunities.  <br>Research & evaluation – Assist in evaluating business growth opportunities through comprehensive industry, client and prospect research. Prepare analyses in support of credit submissions including structuring and documentation.  <br>Innovation - Make an impact by assisting in problem solving and finding solution and often going above and beyond in assisting to find a resolution.  <br> Who you Are  <br>You can demonstrate experience in the field.  You understand financial statements and accounting principles includes valuation techniques and cash flow analysis. If you have a knowledge of commercial banking products and service offerings, that would be asset.  <br>You give meaning to data. Research is your thing!  You enjoy analyzing business growth opportunities through comprehensive industry, client and prospect research. You also like taking that analysis and organizing it into support of credit submissions including structuring and documentation  <br>You’re passionate about people. You enjoy building relationships by making an impact on your community and showing clients they’re appreciated by engaging in marketing and outreach activities.  You’ve been able to develop new relationships by getting referrals from existing relationships and centers of influence  <br>You’re motivated by collective success.  You enjoy collaborating with a team to come up with innovative solutions to a problem that will make a difference today and tomorrow.  You also provide guidance on treasury best practices and cash management solutions that will best meet your clients’ needs.  <br>You put our clients first. You consistently put the client first by proactively assessing your clients’ needs and proposing solutions to meet those needs.  Your understanding of business and financial concepts allows you to provide “best in class” service and client/prospect proposals for financial and strategic solutions to meet client needs  <br>You’re goal oriented. You are focused on meeting your goals and delivering your best efforts to make an impact on the client and the team.  <br>You’re a skilled communicator (written and spoken): You’re open to ideas and concepts presented by others. You actively listen to ensure that you’ve understood direction and grasped new information. You genuinely enjoy engaging with co-workers to get work done.  <br>Values matter to you. You want to bring your whole self to work so work for a company that acknowledges everyone’s unique talents and empowers teams to do what’s right.  <br>  What CIBC Offers<br>At CIBC, your goals are a priority. We start with your strengths and ambitions as an employee and strive to create opportunities to tap into your potential. We aspire to give you a career, rather than just a paycheck.<br>We work to recognize you in meaningful, personalized ways including a competitive salary, incentive pay, banking benefits, a benefits program*, defined benefit pension plan*, an employee share purchase plan, a vacation offering, wellbeing support, and MomentMakers, our social, points-based recognition program.<br>Our spaces and technological toolkit will make it simple to bring together great minds to create innovative solutions that make a difference for our clients.<br>We cultivate a culture where you can express your ambition through initiatives like Purpose Day; a paid day off dedicated for you to use to invest in your growth and development.<br>*Subject to plan and program terms and conditions<br>What you need to know<br>CIBC is committed to creating an inclusive environment where all team members and clients feel like they belong. We seek applicants with a wide range of abilities and we provide an accessible candidate experience. If you need accommodation, please contact Mailbox.careers-carrieres@cibc.com<br>You need to be legally eligible to work at the location(s) specified above and, where applicable, must have a valid work or study permit.<br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>Job Location<br>Fort Saint John<br>Employment Type<br>Regular<br>Weekly Hours<br>37.5<br>Skills<br>Business Banking, Business Development, Business Opportunities, Client Service, Customer Experience (CX), Lending, Portfolio Management]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIBC: Data Scientist Co-op]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://cibc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/campus/job/Toronto-ON/Data-Scientist-Co-op_2521735?Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, ON<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 26, 2025 (6 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>2521735<br>We’re building a relationship-oriented bank for the modern world. We need talented, passionate professionals who are dedicated to doing what’s right for our clients.<br>At CIBC, we embrace your strengths and your ambitions, so you are empowered at work. Our team members have what they need to make a meaningful impact and are truly valued for who they are and what they contribute.<br>To learn more about CIBC, please visit CIBC.com<br>What You’ll Be Doing  <br>The Advanced Analytics and AI team is the central hub of data science and AI expertise within CIBC, and is leading the way to apply the best practices in predictive science, machine learning, artificial intelligence and leverage the latest in big data technology platforms. We also engage with the leading academic & research institutes in the space of AI and machine learning to promote the exchange of latest technology developments and enrich our talents. As a Data Scientist Co-op on this team, you will support strategic initiatives, recommending and delivering complex advanced models and AI solutions to support their goals.<br><br>At CIBC we enable the work environment most optimal for you to thrive in your role you’ll have the flexibility to manage your work activities within a hybrid work arrangement where you’ll spend 1-3 days per week on-site, while other days will be remote.<br> Important <br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us. <br>You must be currently enrolled in post-secondary education and returning to full-time studies to be eligible. However, you do not need to be in a registered Co-Op program to be considered for a role. <br>Recruitment timeline: Applications review – September/ October; Interviews – September/ October; Offers – October/ November <br>Please include your resume (no more than 2 pages), a cover letter (no more than 1 page), and your most recent unofficial transcript with your application. These should all be uploaded into the Resume section of the application as one pdf document  <br>This is a 4-month co-op opportunity. <br>How You’ll Succeed  <br>Apply AI & ML to solve real-world problems- You will utilize your knowledge in statistics, machine learning and/or optimization to frame business problems in a data science context. You will build data products by writing code that is modular, reliable, maintainable & replicable.<br>Utilize a consulting mindset when engaging with our partners- You will work closely with our business partners to understand their challenges by asking the right questions to gather information. You will put in the effort to understand the business problem and to answer any questions and concerns brought up by our partners.<br>Remain intellectually curious with a drive to constant improve our techniques and approaches to AI/ML problems- You will collaborate with data experts to learn about data and engineer relevant features. You will effectively collaborate with other data scientists and engineers to work together and build data products.<br>Who You Are <br>You are pursuing a degree in math, engineering, computer science, the natural sciences, other related quantitative field, or equivalent work experience.<br>You demonstrate knowledge of traditional AI/ML techniques in prediction, classification, forecasting, optimization, Natural Language Processing (NLP).<br>You have familiarity or experience with modern data science, machine learning and AI/ML toolkits, such as Pandas, scikit-learn, XGBoost, spaCy, Keras & Huggingface/Transformers. An understanding of GenAI and LLMs with a working knowledge of fine-tuning, RAG patterns, agentic workflows.<br>You have familiarity of API frameworks, such as Flask and FastAPI, as well as containerization technologies, such as Docker. Knowledge of operations based use cases involving document extraction & OCR is a big asset.<br>You have a working knowledge of Azure based cloud AI services and frameworks.<br>You are a problem solver. You have exceptional critical thinking, problem solving, and decision making skills with demonstrated ability to independently identify and analyze problems and recommend solutions. You are passionate about the responsible and ethical use of AI to benefit society. You enjoy conducting research, developing processes and guidance, and educating others on this important topic.<br>Values matter to you. You bring your real self to work and you live our values – trust, teamwork, and accountability.<br>What CIBC Offers<br>At CIBC, your goals are a priority. We start with your strengths and ambitions as an employee and strive to create opportunities to tap into your potential.<br>We work to recognize you in meaningful, personalized ways including a competitive compensation, a banking benefit*, wellbeing support and additional offers such as employee and family assistance programs and MomentMakers, our social, points-based recognition program.<br>Our spaces and technological toolkit will make it simple to bring together great minds to create innovative solutions that make a difference for our clients.<br>*Subject to program terms and conditions<br>What you need to know<br>CIBC is committed to creating an inclusive environment where all team members and clients feel like they belong. We seek applicants with a wide range of abilities and we provide an accessible candidate experience. If you need accommodation, please contact Mailbox.careers-carrieres@cibc.com<br>You need to be legally eligible to work at the location(s) specified above and, where applicable, must have a valid work or study permit<br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>Expected End Date<br>2026-04-24<br>Job Location<br>Toronto-81 Bay, 21st Floor<br>Employment Type<br>Temporary (Fixed Term)<br>Weekly Hours<br>37.5<br>Skills<br>Computer Science, Consulting, Data Science, Machine Learning]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIBC: Identity Theft Representative, Fraud, Remote- Bilingual]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://cibc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/campus/job/Montral-QC/Identity-Theft-Representative--Fraud--Remote--Bilingual_2521623?Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Montréal, QC<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>2521623<br>We’re building a relationship-oriented bank for the modern world. We need talented, passionate professionals who are dedicated to doing what’s right for our clients.<br>At CIBC, we embrace your strengths and your ambitions, so you are empowered at work. Our team members have what they need to make a meaningful impact and are truly valued for who they are and what they contribute.<br>To learn more about CIBC, please visit CIBC.com<br>What you'll be doing  <br> You’ll work in the Fraud Credit and Debit cards Contact Centre team. As an Fraud Agent, you will be responsible for ensuring the delivery of service to both External and Internal customers consistent with CIBC’s vision of winning customer loyalty through service excellence. You’ll use extensive analytical ability, resolve all complex or difficult problems relating to Fraud Applications, Account Takeovers, Convenience Cheques, and Payments referred by other areas of CIBC or other external sources as well as from our monitoring systems.<br>Please note that the start date is December 1st, 2025 and it's a full time permanent position. A quick note on your availability – our Contact Centre is open Monday to Sunday, 7:00 am to midnight. We’d like for you to be flexible between these hours. <br>At CIBC we enable the work environment most optimal for you to thrive in your role. You can effectively perform all work activities remotely, and will only be required to be on-site on an occasional basis.<br>We have embarked on an Agent@Home remote work program. All employees are required to meet the Agent@Home program requirements and be able to attend your primary work location within two hours’ notice for any business-related purposes.<br>Agent@Home Program Requirements:<br>Ability to work independently as an Agent@Home with a secure workspace, in a room or office with a door that closes it off from noises and distractions. <br>Wired Internet connection, capable of continuously supporting excellent call quality and high-speed response rate (Internet connection can be connected to modem through hard cable (not wireless) with a minimum download speed of 15 mbps and upload speed of 10 mbps) <br>Satellite internet providers are prohibited and cannot be used due to the impact on call quality and the stability of service<br>How you'll succeed  <br>Investigation- Identify suspected fraudulent activities using knowledge of risk management principles, policies and procedures to mitigate fraud and minimize losses to CIBC & in an efficient and timely manner to meet productivity goals. <br>Analysis – Use sound decision making skills to react quickly to incoming calls/referrals and make sound decisions in situations where limited information/ambiguity exists including reviewing customer’s profiles, transactions and banking history to minimize exposure to loss, and protect CIBC and our clients privacy<br>Collaboration – Identify, refer and escalate different types of fraud to relevant areas within the Identity Theft Response Fraud Contact Center to, Fraud Strategy, Corporate Security, Loss Management, Client Care, Ombudsman Office, VISA, and Intria) to be effectively investigated and resolved.<br>Who you are  <br>You can demonstrate experience in COINS/ECIF, PRM, TSYS and CRS is an asset. <br>You put our clients first. You engage with purpose to find the right solutions. You go the extra mile, because it's the right thing to do.<br>You understand that success is in the details. You notice things that others don't. Your critical thinking skills help to inform your decision making<br>You act like an owner. You thrive when you're empowered to take the lead, go above and beyond and deliver results<br>Values matter to you. You bring your real self to work and you live our values – trust, teamwork and accountability<br>You're fluent in French and English to serve our clients in the community.<br>What CIBC Offers<br>At CIBC, your goals are a priority. We start with your strengths and ambitions as an employee and strive to create opportunities to tap into your potential. We aspire to give you a career, rather than just a paycheck.<br>We work to recognize you in meaningful, personalized ways including a competitive salary, incentive pay, banking benefits, a benefits program*, defined benefit pension plan*, an employee share purchase plan, a vacation offering, wellbeing support, and MomentMakers, our social, points-based recognition program.<br>Our spaces and technological toolkit will make it simple to bring together great minds to create innovative solutions that make a difference for our clients.<br>We cultivate a culture where you can express your ambition through initiatives like Purpose Day; a paid day off dedicated for you to use to invest in your growth and development.<br>*Subject to plan and program terms and conditions<br>What you need to know<br>CIBC is committed to creating an inclusive environment where all team members and clients feel like they belong. We seek applicants with a wide range of abilities and we provide an accessible candidate experience. If you need accommodation, please contact Mailbox.careers-carrieres@cibc.com<br>You need to be legally eligible to work at the location(s) specified above and, where applicable, must have a valid work or study permit.<br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>Job Location<br>Mont-1155 Rene Levesque 7th<br>Employment Type<br>Regular<br>Weekly Hours<br>37.5<br>Skills<br>Call Center, Client Service, Communication, Credit Card Fraud, Customer Experience (CX), Outbound Calls, Work Collaboratively]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIBC: Business Systems Analyst Co-op]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://cibc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/campus/job/Toronto-ON/Business-Systems-Analyst-Co-op_2521718?Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, ON<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 26, 2025 (6 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>2521718<br>We’re building a relationship-oriented bank for the modern world. We need talented, passionate professionals who are dedicated to doing what’s right for our clients.<br>At CIBC, we embrace your strengths and your ambitions, so you are empowered at work. Our team members have what they need to make a meaningful impact and are truly valued for who they are and what they contribute.<br>To learn more about CIBC, please visit CIBC.com<br>What you’ll be doing <br>Join our CIBC Technology Operations Team as a Business Systems Analyst Co-op. In this role, you will support end-to end project implementation in technology. You’ll ideate and collaborate with a diverse team in Infrastructure Operations and Networking to create and set up flexible, innovative solutions that deliver a best in-class client experience. <br>At CIBC we enable the work environment most optimal for you to thrive in your role. Details on your work arrangement (proportion of on-site and remote work) will be discussed at the time of your interview.<br>Important information <br> Please note, we have multiple positions available under this posting and you may be considered by more than one hiring team <br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>You must be currently enrolled in post-secondary education and returning to full-time studies to be eligible. However, you do not need to be in a registered Co-Op program to be considered for a role.<br>Please include your resume (no more than 2 pages), a cover letter (no more than 1 page), and your most recent unofficial transcript with your application. These should all be uploaded into the Resume section of the application as one pdf document .<br>This is a 8 month opportunity.<br>How you’ll succeed <br>Understanding Requirements – Posses strong communication skills, exceptional organizational abilities, and a proven track record of excelling in independent work. Excel proficiency is a must.<br>Relationship Building – establishing relationships with Technology Partners, Colleagues and Managers to ensure strong partnerships and cooperative learning spaces.<br>Projects – be part of complex projects to design strategic solutions aligned to CIBC’s enterprise architecture roadmap <br>Who you are <br>Communication. You have excellent verbal and written communication skills to effectively articulate ideas and opinions that involve analysis, interpretation, and assessment.<br>Data analytics. You have the technical skills to review and evaluate data to find innovative opportunities and share with partners<br>Process Improvement. You enjoy the process of researching current processes and identifying improvements that will optimize or improve standards<br>Creativity. You are curious and enjoy working in a team to visualize and design a possible new product or service and to assess the market, business and technical merits of that concept<br>Problem Solving. You enjoy being presented with problems or issues and working with a team to find innovative solutions<br>Values matter to you. You bring your real self to work and you live our values – trust, teamwork and accountability  <br>What CIBC Offers<br>At CIBC, your goals are a priority. We start with your strengths and ambitions as an employee and strive to create opportunities to tap into your potential.<br>We work to recognize you in meaningful, personalized ways including a competitive compensation, a banking benefit*, wellbeing support, and additional offers such as employee and family assistance programs and MomentMakers, our social, points-based recognition program.<br>Our spaces and technological toolkit will make it simple to bring together great minds to create innovative solutions that make a difference for our clients.<br>*Subject to program terms and conditions<br>What you need to know<br>CIBC is committed to creating an inclusive environment where all team members and clients feel like they belong. We seek applicants with a wide range of abilities and we provide an accessible candidate experience. If you need accommodation, please contact Mailbox.careers-carrieres@cibc.com<br>You need to be legally eligible to work at the location(s) specified above and, where applicable, must have a valid work or study permit.<br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>Job Location<br>Toronto-81 Bay, 27th Floor<br>Employment Type<br>Temporary (Fixed Term)<br>Weekly Hours<br>37.5<br>Skills<br>Collaborating, Teamwork, Written Communication]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[CIBC: AI Scientist Co-op]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://cibc.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/campus/job/Toronto-ON/AI-Scientist-Co-op_2521716?Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, ON<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 26, 2025 (6 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>2521716<br>We’re building a relationship-oriented bank for the modern world. We need talented, passionate professionals who are dedicated to doing what’s right for our clients.<br>At CIBC, we embrace your strengths and your ambitions, so you are empowered at work. Our team members have what they need to make a meaningful impact and are truly valued for who they are and what they contribute.<br>To learn more about CIBC, please visit CIBC.com<br>What you'll be doing <br>CIBC’s Enterprise Advanced Analytics and AI team is hiring an AI Scientist. The Enterprise Advanced Analytics team is a central hub of data science expertise within CIBC and is leading the way in applying the best practices in predictive science, machine learning, leveraging massive datasets and the latest in big data technology platforms. In this role, you will work with real world structured and unstructured datasets to produce end-to-end solutions, taking models from experiment to deployment. We collaborate with the most exciting new companies in the space of AI and machine learning and engage in teamwork with leading academic researchers to promote the exchange of ideas and enrich our talent. <br>At CIBC we enable the work environment most optimal for you to thrive in your role. Details on your work arrangement (proportion of on-site and remote work) will be discussed at the time of your interview <br>Important <br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us. <br>You must be currently enrolled in post-secondary education and returning to full-time studies to be eligible. However, you do not need to be in a registered Co-Op program to be considered for a role. <br>Recruitment timeline: Applications review – September/ October; Interviews – September/ October ; Offers – October/ November <br>Please include your resume (no more than 2 pages), a cover letter (no more than 1 page), and your most recent unofficial transcript with your application. These should all be uploaded into the Resume section of the application as one pdf document <br>We have 4 and 8 month openings. <br>How you'll succeed <br>Coding Expertise: You will schema back-end development and organization of data onto a database, UX design front end to back end solutioning, manage single sign on capabilities, perform and coordinate complex application programming activities, design the application's technical infrastructure using specific databases, programming languages, utilities, and testing approaches, lead the design and development of cost-effective and innovative solutions and lead code-review sessions with the wider team to ensure the project is on track to meet objectives. <br>MLOps: You will utilize your Python programming skills to refactor experimental notebooks into production grade Python modules using functional programming. You will assist with tasks related to the deployment of machine learning models and the maintenance of internal Python libraries   <br>Champion Best Practices: You will adhere to the team’s code-style, work-flow patterns and project structure standards. You will participate in writing great documentation, practicing test-driven-development and properly annotating your code. <br>Who you are <br>You have strong Tech Skills: You demonstrate good programming skills and have knowledge of SQL API web development. You have knowledge of languages: HTML, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS/Sass, ES6, Python. Knowledge of Front-end apps like Angular, Bootstrap, React, Vue and Back-end - Node.js, Express.js, Django. Knowledge of Databases: SQL, Mongo, Cosmos and  Operating Systems: Linux, Windows. Knowledge of other technologies like Git, Docker, JSON, REST APIs, RxJS/Redux, jQuery, Azure and Machine Learning algorithms understanding is asset. <br>You're driven by collective success. You know that collaboration can transform a good idea into a great one. You understand the power of an inclusive team that enjoys working together to bring a shared vision to life. <br>You have a strong sense of intellectual curiosity. You are intellectually curious and often think about ways to improve how we work. You may not know every tool or framework, but your innate sense of curiosity drives you to learn and grow your technical and business acumen. <br>Values matter to you. You bring your real self to work and you live our values – trust, teamwork and accountability.  <br> What CIBC Offers<br>At CIBC, your goals are a priority. We start with your strengths and ambitions as an employee and strive to create opportunities to tap into your potential.<br>We work to recognize you in meaningful, personalized ways including a competitive compensation, a banking benefit*, wellbeing support and additional offers such as employee and family assistance programs and MomentMakers, our social, points-based recognition program.<br>Our spaces and technological toolkit will make it simple to bring together great minds to create innovative solutions that make a difference for our clients.<br>*Subject to program terms and conditions<br>What you need to know<br>CIBC is committed to creating an inclusive environment where all team members and clients feel like they belong. We seek applicants with a wide range of abilities and we provide an accessible candidate experience. If you need accommodation, please contact Mailbox.careers-carrieres@cibc.com<br>You need to be legally eligible to work at the location(s) specified above and, where applicable, must have a valid work or study permit<br>We may ask you to complete an attribute-based assessment and other skills tests (such as simulation, coding, French proficiency, MS Office). Our goal for the application process is to get to know more about you, all that you have to offer, and give you the opportunity to learn more about us.<br>Expected End Date<br>2026-04-24<br>Job Location<br>Toronto-81 Bay, 21st Floor<br>Employment Type<br>Temporary (Fixed Term)<br>Weekly Hours<br>37.5<br>Skills<br>CSS Scripting, Data Science, JavaScript, JSON, Machine Learning, Python (Programming Language), SQL Databases, User Experience (UX) Design]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Technical Product Owner]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Technical-Product-Owner_JR25090055-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 25, 2025 (5 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090055<br>The Opportunity<br>This position is for a Senior Technical Product Owner within Manulife’s Products and Platforms team.<br>We are seeking a talented, motivated and driven individual who will be responsible for being a Product Owner of Cloud and AI based automation development Agile Scrum Development Squad(s) for better Developer and User experience. You will be creating user stories, prioritizing backlog and performing agile scrum ceremonies for Agile scrum squad(s). This will be through engagement with application owners, developers, cloud operations and security teams, product managers, engineering team and leadership. You will also be responsible for developing deliverable/release technical content for stakeholder consumption.<br>You will interact cross-functionally with engineering, product managers, cloud operations team and internal business segments.<br>People Leader Role: No<br>Office Location: Toronto – Canada  or  Boston - USA<br>Work arrangement: Hybrid - 3 days in office, 2 days from Home; Remote working option is not available.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Responsible for being a Product Owner of Agile development scrum team(s).<br>Creates and maintains a prioritized scrum team backlog based on business value, ROI and company vision.<br>Responsible for Elaboration of User stories.<br>Work both internally with functional groups (engineering, product managers, cloud operations team and internal business segments) to drive technical release content and deliverables.<br>Engage with customers on an occasional basis, solicit requirements and prioritize backlog accordingly.<br>Deliver Solution Presentations/Demos at internal and external business reviews and meetings.<br>Create technical content for stakeholder consumption<br>Required Qualifications: <br>Experience in product owner responsibilities focused on Public Cloud Services, Software, Automation and Orchestration tools.<br>Technical knowledge in Cloud automation, Devsecops and Application/Platform/Infrastructure security and monitoring tools preferred.<br>Knowledge of AI and Low code/No Code Agentic AI development platforms such as Microsoft Copilot Studio and other AI development tools such as GitHub Copilot, is desired.<br>Experience with Agile development/Scrum methodologies required.<br>Leadership skills to take new challenges and creativity to take new approaches to problems<br>BS or equivalent required.<br>Prior Product Owner background in software development and/or IT projects required.<br>Product Owner certification required<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Large Complex environment experience is highly desired but not a must have<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$94,220.00 CAD - $174,980.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Bilingual, National Field Underwriting Consultant]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/CAN-Quebec---Full-Time-Remote/National-Field-Underwriting-Consultant_JR25080787-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>CAN, Quebec - Full Time Remote<br>CAN, Ontario, Waterloo, 500 King Street North<br>CAN, Quebec, Montreal, 900 Boulevard de Maisonneuve Ouest<br>CAN, Ontario, Toronto, 200 Bloor Street East<br>CAN, Nova Scotia, Halifax, 2727 Joseph Howe Drive<br>View All 6 Locations<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 7, 2025 (17 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25080787<br>The bilingual Regional Field Underwriter is a key member of Manulife’s renowned Underwriting team, operating at the intersection of field-level collaboration and innovative underwriting practices. This role involves working closely with advisors, clients, and wholesalers, providing expert medical and financial field underwriting services, including case packaging and cover memo preparation. The Regional Field Underwriter plays a crucial role in supporting our Summit Experience and enhancing client satisfaction and business growth through excellence in field underwriting.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>Conduct risk assessment and classification in alignment with Manulife's philosophy and standards.<br>Proactively and reactively support advisors and clients, particularly with large life insurance cases over $5 million.<br>Enhance sales through strong advisor relationships and excellence in field underwriting practices.<br>Prepare comprehensive cover letters and respond to preliminary opinions and inquiries promptly.<br>Engage directly with clients to provide curated preliminary opinions.<br>Collaborate with the National Field Underwriter and Head Office underwriters to ensure consistency and the highest quality decisions.<br>Maintain positive and effective relationships with internal and external partners, including advisors, wholesalers, and other specialists.<br>Stay updated with industry trends and guidelines by attending underwriting and sales team meetings.<br>Manage client expectations by identifying unwanted risks and suggesting alternative product solutions.<br>Align with consumer laws and regulations regarding risk classification, confidentiality, and disclosure.<br>Identify and propose solutions to enhance processes and customer experience.<br>Create and deliver presentations and conduct regular in-person meetings to strengthen advisor relationships.<br>Represent Manulife externally.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>Minimum of 15 years of experience as an underwriter, specializing in large life insurance cases over $5 million.<br>Proven track record in underwriting with a sales and relationship-focused mindset.<br>Strong understanding of insurance products, financial and medical guidelines, and non-medical risks impacting mortality.<br>Experience with financial reports and training in anti-money laundering practices.<br>Ability to work collaboratively with advisors, wholesalers, and underwriters, and think creatively to provide solutions.<br>Proficiency in Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel, and Teams.<br>Strong time management, organizational skills, and ability to analyze complex information.<br>Fully bilingual (French/English): The successful candidate will be required to communicate in English and French in order to support clients from all jurisdictions/provinces within Canada.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Working towards, or completion of FALU, FLMI, and ACS designations.<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want. <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words. <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Remote<br>Salary & Benefits<br>Salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance. Please contact recruitment@manulife.com for additional information.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Consolidation Coordinator]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Atlanta-Georgia/Consolidation-Coordinator_JR25071582-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Atlanta, Georgia<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 3, 2025 (13 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25071582<br>The Consolidation Coordinator is a dynamic and pivotal role within our bustling inbound/outbound phone center, dedicated to transforming participants' retirement experiences by seamlessly consolidating their external retirement accounts into John Hancock 401ks.<br>As a Consolidation Coordinator, you will be the trusted guide for John Hancock participants, expertly navigating them through the consolidation process to ensure effortless asset management in a single, streamlined account. This thrilling opportunity is perfect for anyone eager to launch an exciting career in the retirement industry. Our enthusiastic team will champion your quest to obtain FINRA licenses and provide you with comprehensive education in the ever-evolving retirement plan industry. Join us and be part of a transformative journey!<br>* This is a hybrid role based out of our Atlanta office *<br>Responsibilities:<br>Member of an in-bound/out-bound phone-based team focused on driving new roll-in assets for John Hancock<br>Educate and help 401(k) participants to better understand the benefits of consolidating their retirement assets into their JH 401(k)<br>Assist new and existing 401(k) participants throughout the roll-in process. This would generally include obtaining authorization on rollover paperwork and contacting plan providers, plan administrators, and third-party administrators<br>Qualify opportunities and help follow-up on outstanding cases<br>Work directly with financial intermediaries (Plan Consultants (TPAs) and Financial Advisors) and ultimately channel roll-in business into the JH 401(k) plan<br>Deliver superior service in a professional manner<br>Enter and prioritize workflows necessary to track potential roll-in opportunities<br>Share successful education and process improvement ideas in a team environment<br>Proactively share knowledge to ensure team objectives are met<br>Other duties as assigned<br><br>Key Shared Responsibilities:<br>Contributing to team goals<br>Taking inbound calls as necessary<br>Handling smaller, segmented cases<br>Required Qualifications:<br>Bachelor’s Degree with a focus on Business and/or Finance<br>FINRA Series 6 and 63 required within 6 months of hire<br>Some financial services industry experience preferred<br>Ability to efficiently promote the benefits of the program and the services we provide<br>Strong service and overall communication/negotiation skills <br>Ability to consult with all customers<br>Ability to succeed in a team environment<br>Detail oriented with the ability to prioritize and remain organized in a multiple task environment<br>Being able to work independently toward mutual goals/targets<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>#LI-JH<br>#LI-Hybrid<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary & Benefits<br>Salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance. Please contact recruitment@manulife.com for additional information.<br>Manulife/John Hancock offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension/401(k) savings plans and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in the U.S. includes up to 11 paid holidays, 3 personal days, 150 hours of vacation, and 40 hours of sick time (or more where required by law) each year, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence.<br>Know Your Rights  I Family & Medical Leave I Employee Polygraph Protection I Right to Work I E-Verify I Pay Transparency<br>Company: John Hancock Life Insurance Company (U.S.A.)]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Bilingual Policy Specialist, Policy Change]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/CAN-Quebec---Full-Time-Remote/Bilingual-Policy-Specialist---Policy-Change_JR25090478?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>CAN, Quebec - Full Time Remote<br>Montreal, Quebec<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 3, 2025 (13 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090478<br>The Policy Specialist will be reporting to the Supervisor in Legacy Operations and will be responsible for handling transactions with various levels of complexity. <br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Reviews and/or processes received transactions accurately and in a timely manner. <br>Provide excellent service to internal and external clients, whether by email, phone calls, or correspondence. Respond to inquiries received from internal and external clients, after appropriate research and analysis. To do this, find the best way to solve the problem and accurately process the necessary operations. <br>Collaborate with teams located in various offices to achieve dynamic volumes and meet service standards. <br>Demonstrates a positive attitude in finding solutions to problems. <br>Contribute to the optimization of service efficiency by suggesting process improvements. <br>Collaborates effectively with the other departments within Policy Services <br>Consistently meet or exceed productivity, quality and service standard objectives.  <br>Multi-task and prioritize daily to maintain workload and to address urgent/rush cases.  <br>Ability to perform a wide range of tasks across the business area  <br>Consistent demonstration of flexibility and adaptability in a rapidly changing environment.  <br>Confidently communicate (written or phone) with internal, external clients, sponsors, agents, and brokers in a courteous and professional manner  <br>Routinely demonstrate ownership and accountability of all requests in a proactive rather than reactive manner.  <br>Required Qualifications: <br>Bilingualism (French and English) is a prerequisite <br>College diploma or equivalent experience <br>Strong decision-making and interpersonal skills <br>Excellent verbal and written communication <br>Ability to work independently and manage multiple tasks <br>Highly organized with attention to detail <br>Adaptable to fast-paced environments <br>Strong customer service orientation <br>Proactive and self-motivated<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want. <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words. <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>#LI-Hybrid<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>CAN, Quebec - Full Time Remote<br>Working Arrangement<br>Remote<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$44,775.00 CAD - $74,625.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Graduate Recruitment Opportunities (GRO) - Investment Management (Toronto)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Graduate-Recruitment-Opportunities--GRO----Investment-Management_JR25071634?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 4, 2025 (14 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25071634<br>Graduate Recruitment Opportunities (GRO) at Manulife John Hancock. Start your career with purpose, growth, and community. <br>At Manulife John Hancock, we believe in investing in the future—starting with you. Our Graduate Recruitment Opportunities (GRO) program is a bold new approach to early talent development, designed to launch your career with the support, structure, and opportunities you need to thrive. GRO is Manulife John Hancock ’s flagship early talent program and brand. It’s more than just a job—it’s a launchpad for your career. GRO offers a consistent, high-quality experience for new graduates across the organization.<br><br>Shape the future of investing with our Investment Management Program, a key stream within our GRO early talent program. This dynamic two-year rotational program is designed to develop high-potential graduates into future leaders in investment and asset management. Through two 12-month rotations across areas like Real Estate Asset Management, Multi-Asset Strategies (MAST), Infrastructure Equity, Fixed Income Research, and Private Markets Product Development, you’ll gain broad exposure to the investment landscape while building a strong foundation for your career. As part of GRO, you’ll benefit from mentorship, leadership access, and a collaborative community that supports your growth and helps you discover your passion for the world of investments.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Gain valuable and diverse experience with multiple asset classes and back, middle, and front office exposure <br>Work with a variety of Assignment Managers to maximize the opportunity to acquire technical knowledge <br>Develop an appreciation of the diversity of the asset origination and asset management businesses within the context of a large global financial services firm <br> <br>Required Qualifications: <br>Expected to graduate in 2026 from an accredited university with a degree in Finance, Economics, or Business Administration <br>Working knowledge of investment and financial markets <br>Demonstrated understanding of financial and investment analysis techniques <br>Ability to be flexible, creative, and proactive in a challenging and fast-paced environment <br>Strong written and verbal communication skills <br>Proficient in Excel, Word, and PowerPoint, with a strong ability to learn new software quickly <br>Familiarity with both quantitative and qualitative statistical analysis <br>  <br>When you join our team:  <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.   <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.   <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>Application Instructions:   <br>Please submit a resume, cover letter and most recent transcript (unofficial transcripts are accepted) in one PDF file<br>*This position is subject to the Securities and Exchange Commission's Pay-to-Play Rule 206(4)-5 regarding political contributions by investment advisers and their covered associates.  This position requires compliance with the rules and applicable company policies on political contributions.  The absence of certain political contributions is a condition of this position.  Candidates will be required to disclose political contribution activity which will be subject to review to ensure compliance with the rule, as a pre-condition to employment. Additionally, this position is subject to a code of ethics as a condition of employment.  Once hired, the code imposes restrictions and obligations on the candidate and the candidate's household members regarding their personal securities investment activities as well as prohibiting the use of certain brokerage firms.  <br> #LI-Hybrid<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$60,375.00 USD - $100,625.00 USD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Financial Analyst – Investor Relations]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Financial-Analyst---Investor-Relations_JR25091095-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 6, 2025 (16 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091095<br>The Investor Relations (IR) team is primarily responsible for ongoing communication with the investment community including existing and prospective institutional shareholders, as well as sell side equity research analysts.  The team’s mandate also includes providing market intelligence to internal partners.<br>The Senior Financial Analyst - Investor Relations provides key analytical and marketing support to the IR team and would assist in a number of areas including monitoring and summarizing analyst and industry reports, conducting industry research and peer reviews, preparing materials for investor engagement events, as well as assisting in quarter end deliverables and special projects and initiatives.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Quarterly Analysis and Reporting: Summarize analysts' sentiments and reports pre- and post-earnings, analyze peer earnings calls, and prepare Board reports covering IR activities, goals, analyst sentiment, stock performance, and holdings<br>Quarter end Reporting: Assist with drafting of earnings press releases, develop analyst slides, and speaking notes for earnings calls/webcasts, and other quarterly deliverables such as company fact sheets<br>IR Website and Sharepoint Management: Manage content and aesthetics of the IR website, maintain IR Sharepoint content and user access, and lead Records Management within IR.<br>Market and Financial Analysis: Conduct research and market analysis using IR tools (e.g., Bloomberg, NASDAQ IRI), review communication materials to ensure best practices, and prepare materials for marketing road shows<br>Strategic Projects and Initiatives: Initiate and complete strategic projects using internal and external resources, assist with IR marketing efforts, maintaining investor targeting models, and develop short-term and long-term IR marketing plans<br>Ad-hoc Requests and Special Projects: Participate in ad hoc or special projects as required, ensuring alignment with overall strategic goals and employing available resources<br>Collaborate extensively with internal partners to collect input, communicate feedback and influence as required. Communicate with external stakeholders professionally as a representative of the company<br>Required Qualifications:<br>1-3 years or more, of progressive work experience in the financial services industry<br>Ability to learn quickly and act nimbly; demonstrated time management and organizational skills. Ability to work within tight and changing time constraints and to handle several tasks at one time<br>Ability to work independently and as part of a team with a high commitment to internal and external customer service<br>Strong judgment and initiative in anticipating and solving issues<br>Strong attention to detail and analytical skills<br>Strong written and verbal communication skills<br>Ability to employ external data sources and tools to complete day-to-day activities; proficient with Microsoft tool set<br>Curiosity and skills to learn and adapt, with a continuous improvement attitude<br>Preferred Qualifications: <br>Undergraduate degree in finance or accounting; CPA or CFA an asset<br>Working understanding of the insurance and/or wealth asset management business and/or Manulife’s products and distribution strategies an asset<br>Prior work experience directly in or adjacent to investor relations function an asset<br>Strong working knowledge of financial reporting required; management reporting skills an asset<br>Familiarity with Bloomberg or NASDAQ IRI, prior experience in financial modeling and charting would be an asset<br>When you join our team: <br>We'll empower you to learn and grow the career you want<br>We'll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words<br>As part of the global team, we'll support you in the shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$71,925.00 CAD - $119,875.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Manager, WAM Reporting & Analysis]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Manager--WAM-Reporting---Analysis_JR25080728-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Waterloo, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 1, 2025 (11 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25080728<br>The Global Wealth and Asset Management (WAM) Financial Planning & Analysis (FP&A) team provides accurate and timely reporting and analysis to stakeholders, including business divisions, Group Finance, Investor Relations, the Board of Directors, and external parties. The team focuses on enhancing the delivery model, driving operational improvements, and operating a Planning and Reporting Centre of Expertise (CoE) for thought leadership and planning figures. It also liaises with Transformation and Accounting and Reporting teams to ensure seamless operations.<br>Reporting to Director, Head of GWAM FP&A the incumbent will be a Finance professional who will take a key role in supporting the fast-growing GWAM franchise by delivering accurate, timely, and relevant reporting and analysis to support Business Unit (BU) and senior management decision making.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Acquiring deep institutional knowledge of GWAM business divisions across the company: Retail (mutual funds), Retirement and Institutional Advisory by partnering with the other finance teams<br>Employing in-house and industry knowledge to provide research and financial analysis resulting in value insights and recommendations to GWAM Heads of Finance and General Managers. This includes supporting the development of new reports, metrics, and analyses that will enable senior executives to make informed decisions on a timely basis<br>Producing thoughtful, relevant management reporting materials for GWAM BUs, Group Finance, Strategy, Investor Relations, the Board of Directors, and external partners, underpinned by a broad understanding of the wealth and asset management industry and competitive landscape<br>Leadership role in consolidating, analyzing, and synthesizing large amount of complex financial and non-financial information from numerous suppliers from GWAM BU Finance and Reporting teams.<br>Prepare and deliver high-quality monthly and quarterly reports, dashboards, and presentations for GWAM BU and Regional heads, ensuring timeliness and organization<br>Contribute to strategic discussions by providing financial insights, business trends, and quantifiable support, aligning with GWAM objectives<br>Act as a GWAM Subject Matter Expert on cross-company initiatives, providing specific insights and mentoring junior finance team members to develop talent<br>Develop and implement a best-in-class reporting framework with financial and non-financial metrics to support differentiation, growth, and forward-looking decisions<br>Maintain strong attention to detail, focusing on financial integrity and ensuring consistency in deliverables<br>Lead continuous improvements by identifying and implementing solutions in reporting, analysis, and processes<br>Collaborate effectively with partners and stakeholders, building relationships and understanding their challenges<br>Required Qualifications:<br>University degree in Accounting/Finance or equivalent<br>Professional accounting designation (CPA) or Degree specialized in Accounting/Finance preferred<br>6-8 years of experience in a finance role; Wealth and Asset Management industry experience an asset<br>Skilled in developing, evaluating, and using financial models, analyzing risks, and displaying strong analytical abilities with a focus on critical thinking and attention to detail.<br>Strong Excel and PowerPoint skills; Essbase/ledger expert would be an asset<br>Demonstrated success in high-performing, fast-paced, collaborative environments, adept at managing multiple priorities and ad-hoc requests<br>Proactive and positive attitude towards continuous improvement, with a curiosity to identify, investigate, and resolve complex issues<br>Strong analytical and critical thinking skills, with experience in writing, analysis, and effective storytelling for deck production<br>Advanced executive communication and writing skills, capable of engaging succinctly with management and team members<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$86,250.00 CAD - $155,250.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior AEM Front-End Engineer - Global Design System]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/AEM-Front-End-Engineer---Global-Design-System_JR25061606?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 3, 2025 (13 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25061606<br>As Senior AEM Front-End Engineer - Global Design System at Manulife, your primary responsibility is translating design specifications into functional, reusable react based components. You will be responsible for coding, maintaining, documenting and driving adoption of components that serves multiple business units across North America and Asia. This system will enable consistency, efficiency, accessibility, and innovation across Manulife’s public, secure, and mobile digital experiences. You will partner closely with engineering, design, and product teams across regions to build components to their requirements, and evolve the system to meet diverse business and customer needs.<br>Position Responsibilities:  <br>Building and maintaining reusable UI components, ensuring consistency across applications in our enterprise-grade design system that supports Manulife’s digital transformation across all regions<br>Collaborating with designers and other developers to define and implement design system specifications<br>Contributing to the overall software development cycle for Manulife’s Global Design System React component library, including mobile apps, web, and CMS<br>Maintaining the design system's code, documentation, and tokens, including updating components, adding new ones, and addressing bugs<br>Balancing global standardization with regional flexibility, ensuring usability across diverse markets and regulatory landscapes<br>Ensuring all components and the overall design system adhere to accessibility standards (e.g., WCAG)<br>Required Qualifications: <br>5 to 8 years of industry experience in technology, preferably within a global enterprise or multi-jurisdictional organization using React with Javascript and/or Typescript in a production enterprise environment.<br>Understanding of AEM Developer tools (Oak repository, JCR API, Apache Sling and OSGi frameworks, etc)<br>Experience with Maven for build automation<br>Experience with Web Components is an asset<br>High degree of experience in React JS and working with Design Systems<br>Hands-on experience delivering front-end solutions<br>Practical experience with Responsive Design and Single Page Application development using standard methodologies and modern frameworks like React and Angular<br>Required certifications from Adobe<br>Demonstrated use of modern CSS and HTML practices to build performant and accessible web experiences<br>Experience with web accessibility compliance, performance, and cross-device support<br>Understanding of modern front-end build tooling (Rollup, ESlint, etc.)<br>Preferred Qualifications: <br>Experience with alternative JS frameworks (Angular, Vue) is a plus<br>Strong expertise in Agile, Lean UX, and enterprise digital delivery models<br>Experience navigating multi-lingual, multi-cultural, and regulatory complexities in global design and technology<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want. <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words. <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>#LI-Hybrid<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$75,880.00 CAD - $140,920.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Director of Finance, Canada Operations]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Director-of-Finance--Canada-Operations_JR25090643?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Waterloo, Ontario<br>Halifax, Nova Scotia<br>Montreal, Quebec<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 6, 2025 (16 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090643<br>The Operations Finance team provides crucial financial advice and support to Global Operations, including the Global COO and leadership team, by delivering comprehensive financial data and insights, maintaining expense policy, and ensuring a strong internal control environment for risk management. Reporting to the AVP, Global Operations Finance, this position acts as a trusted advisor to Canada Operations leaders, managing a team to support finance activities and collaborating with Expense Directors for actionable analysis on expenses, budgets, and financial outlooks. The role involves keeping management informed through formal reviews and linking expense drivers across products and divisions. Additionally, the position plays a key role in supporting transformation efforts within Operations and the FP&A team, serving as the primary finance representative for project reporting and central initiatives.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Expense advisory services: Support business through recurring monthly finance reviews, business case reviews, and other ad hoc analysis<br>FP&A Leadership and Expense Management: Serve as the primary FP&A lead for Canada Operations, responsible for forecasting, budgeting, and results reporting<br>Finance Representation: Act as the key expense representative for global initiatives and partner with the initiative owners to ensure financial transparency of benefits and costs into the program. Leverage subject matter experts across the FP&A team where able<br>Reporting: Lead all aspects of the development of reporting which meets the needs of our customers. Provide valuable analysis along with clear and concise commentary on results for our customers<br>Continuous Improvement: Drive continuous improvement in engagement throughout the organization. Drive finance participation and leadership in KPI reporting and analysis including unit cost analysis through partnership with business partners. Look for opportunities to centralize, automate, and streamline where possible<br>Strategic Savings and Reporting: Support the development, tracking, and reporting of major multi-year strategic save initiatives with consolidated reporting by segment, leader, and savings type, ensuring accountability and addressing risks<br>Required Qualifications <br>10+ years of relevant experience in progressive accounting roles. <br>University degree in business, finance or equivalent<br>Strong interpersonal skills, ability to collaborate, and can negotiate and influence effectively<br>Results oriented, able to manage expectations, work under tight deadlines and handle contending priorities <br>Solid analytical and technical capability - ability to assimilate/summarize a large amount of information from multiple sources and present in a valuable form for senior management<br>Proficiency with Microsoft 365 tools and ability to learn new applications quickly<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>CPA/MBA highly preferred<br>Self-starter with the ability to work independently, think ‘out of the box’, particularly in the areas requiring sound, independent judgment, problem-solving and analytical skills<br>Excellent customer focus and commitment to quality<br>Strong business insight with ability to communicate complex concepts and results in a clear, concise, easy to understand manner (written and verbal)<br>Smartview, Anaplan and Lawson knowledge (or other complex GL package) would be an asset<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$105,750.00 CAD - $190,350.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Financial Analyst, Global IT Finance]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Financial-Analyst--Global-IT-Finance_JR25090312-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 6, 2025 (16 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090312<br>Reporting to the Director, Global IT Finance, the Senior Financial Analyst (SFA) plays a key role in the IT Finance team in the consolidation of finance activities for the IT Function globally. The successful candidate will need to possess solid analytical and technical capability, as well as the ability to work with people at all levels of the organization across multiple business divisions and markets (US, Canada, Asia, GWAM and Corporate). The core accountabilities are:<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Consolidated reporting: Support the Director, Global IT Finance to prepare accurate, complete and timely production of consolidated financial reports and analysis for the Global IT function including the monthly operating report (MOR). This includes closed loop reporting on progress against targets, and overall success of the program in driving expense and FTE savings<br>Financial Planning & Forecasting: Play a key role in the annual budgeting and planning process and monthly forecasting. This includes partnering with Finance, Technology Strategy and IT segment teams and consolidating information in a clear and concise manner. The SFA is expected to understand the drivers behind numbers and use their analytical skills and critical thinking to tell the story<br>Analysis: Support the Director, Global IT Finance to gather inputs from data sources, perform reconciliation and provide key financial analysis and insights of expenses. Also create high quality visual charts/ graphs for reporting<br>Transformation: Work to continuously identify operational improvements by employing existing tools and find new ways to streamline efficiencies (e.g., standardization of reporting) and simplify/ automate process<br>Required Qualifications:<br>University degree in Finance or Accounting. CPA/CA/MBA Finance preferred<br>3-7 years or more of financial analysis experience<br>Experience in Essbase, Anaplan, Power BI, Any other Data Visualization tools<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$71,925.00 CAD - $119,875.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Director, Colleague Community Engagement]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Director--Community-Investment---US-Segment_JR25060509-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 4, 2025 (14 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25060509<br>Manulife is seeking a strategic and visionary leader to serve as Director, Global Colleague Community Engagement! <br>This role will shape and lead global initiatives that foster a culture of connection, purpose, and belonging across our diverse workforce. The successful candidate will be passionate about creating inclusive communities and driving meaningful colleague engagement aligned with Manulife’s mission and values.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Strategic Leadership: Design and execute a global colleague engagement strategy that reflects Manulife’s purpose, values, and business priorities.<br>Program Development: Lead initiatives that promote volunteerism, social impact, and community involvement, ensuring relevance across geographies and cultures.<br>Cross-Functional Collaboration: Partner with HR, Learning & Development, and Communications to embed community engagement into the full employee lifecycle—from onboarding to leadership development.<br>Stakeholder Engagement: Build strong relationships with internal stakeholders and regional leaders to gather insights, co-create solutions, and ensure alignment.<br>Communications & Storytelling: Develop compelling narratives and communication strategies to showcase community initiatives across internal and external channels.<br>Measurement & Insights: Establish KPIs and leverage data to evaluate program effectiveness, inform strategy, and drive continuous improvement.<br>Team Leadership: Manage and mentor a global team of engagement professionals, fostering innovation, collaboration, and professional growth.<br>Thought Leadership: Stay ahead of global trends in employee experience, community engagement, and social impact, bringing fresh ideas and best practices to the organization.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>A combination of education and progressive experience in employee engagement, organizational development, corporate communications, marketing, or a related field.<br>At least 5 years leading initiatives in employee engagement, community development, or social impact—ideally including global program leadership and people management experience. <br>2-5 years of people leadership experience. <br>Creative, proactive, nimble, and solutions-oriented mindset.<br>Proven ability to influence and collaborate across diverse teams and geographies, with comfort with navigating ambiguity and a large matrixed organization.<br>Strong strategic thinking, communication, and stakeholder management skills.<br>Proficiency in data analysis and using insights to inform decision-making.<br>Preferred Qualifications <br>Experience in insurance or financial services is an asset, though not required.<br>When you join our team: <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.  <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.   <br>#LI-Hybrid <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>Toronto, Ontario<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$105,750.00 CAD - $190,350.00 CAD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in Canada includes holidays, vacation, personal, and sick days, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence. If you are applying for this role in the U.S., please contact recruitment@manulife.com for more information about U.S.-specific paid time off provisions.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Silviculture Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/USA-North-Carolina-Charlotte-Frenette-Building-11016-Rushmore-Drive/Silviculture-Coordinator_JR25040602?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>USA, North Carolina, Charlotte, Frenette Building 11016 Rushmore Drive<br>Shreveport, Louisiana<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 3, 2025 (13 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25040602<br>General Directive: Supports the silviculture program for Manulife Investment Management Forest Management’s (MFM) Southern Division and Lake States.    <br>Scope:<br>MFM-managed properties totaling approximately 2.2 million acres in the Western Gulf, Central South, Mid-Atlantic, Lake States, and Allegheny regions of eastern United States.<br>Decision support for client properties in the Southern Division and Lake States<br>Job Dimensions:<br>Services the information needs of forest operations teams in multiple locations.<br>Reports to General Manger of Silviculture<br>Member of the silviculture team within the southern operations of MFM<br>Specific Duties:<br>Provide expertise and guidance to MFM Operations on current silviculture practice, treatment efficacy, and root-cause problem analysis.<br>Actively participates in and maintains oversight on research cooperative program meetings, obligations, and work plans.<br>Utilizes Geographic Information Systems (GIS) and internal forest management systems to analyze forest information data to improve silvicultural systems and performance.<br>Develop strategies to transfer, deploy, and monitor value-adding silviculture technology with MFM Operations.<br>Manage MFM’s divisional fertilizer, pesticide, seedling procurement programs in collaboration with MFM Operations. Project and data management skills are highly desired.<br>Provide financial analysis and G&Y support.<br>Actively participate in MFM’s forest resource planning program to provide guidance on benefit analysis of the latest silviculture and forest management technologies.<br>Advance Manulife Investment Management Timberland (MIMT) business development objectives including property acquisitions, property disposition strategy, timberland investment analysis and decision support tools, and other strategic business objectives.<br>Support MFM’s conformance with certification requirements and support management systems that enable the advancement of MFM’s forest stewardship commitment.<br>Continuously improve business procedures and provide training and support to ensure the effective deployment and use of property data and business systems by MFM personnel.<br>Job Task Categories by Estimated Time: 40% - Direct Support of MFM Silviculture Operation Program, 30% - Business Analytics for Decision Support, 20% - Research Cooperative Participation, 10% Coordination of Silviculture Operations and Resource Support Team<br>Special projects as requested or needed.<br>Requirements:<br>A Master of Science degree in forestry or related discipline and a minimum of 5 years of professional experience in forest management. A Bachelor of Science with extensive experience will be considered.<br>Strong computer and analytical skills are required. Knowledge of Growth & Yield model systems such as SiMS or other related systems is desired.<br>Demonstrated proficiency in discounted cashflow analysis and other analytic skills to support optimal business decisions.<br>Demonstrated proficiency in Geographic Information Systems with skills to master internal forest information systems. Remote sensing skills using satellite imagery is a plus.<br>Demonstrated proficiency with one or more regional silviculture systems including regeneration, management best practices, management cost and return expectations, discounted cash flow analysis.<br>Knowledgeable of forest certification (SFI), harvesting systems, contracting process, and timber marketing.<br>Must be team player and self-motivated<br>Must have excellent interpersonal, collaboration and communication skills<br>Must be service oriented.<br>Must be willing to travel 20 percent of time<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>#LI-JH-MIMTA <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Referenced Salary Location<br>USA, North Carolina, Charlotte, Frenette Building 11016 Rushmore Drive<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid<br>Salary range is expected to be between<br>$68,175.00 USD - $113,625.00 USD<br>If you are applying for this role outside of the primary location, please contact recruitment@manulife.com for the salary range for your location. The actual salary will vary depending on local market conditions, geography and relevant job-related factors such as knowledge, skills, qualifications, experience, and education/training. Employees also have the opportunity to participate in incentive programs and earn incentive compensation tied to business and individual performance.<br>Manulife/John Hancock offers eligible employees a wide array of customizable benefits, including health, dental, mental health, vision, short- and long-term disability, life and AD&D insurance coverage, adoption/surrogacy and wellness benefits, and employee/family assistance plans. We also offer eligible employees various retirement savings plans (including pension/401(k) savings plans and a global share ownership plan with employer matching contributions) and financial education and counseling resources. Our generous paid time off program in the U.S. includes up to 11 paid holidays, 3 personal days, 150 hours of vacation, and 40 hours of sick time (or more where required by law) each year, and we offer the full range of statutory leaves of absence.<br>Know Your Rights  I Family & Medical Leave I Employee Polygraph Protection I Right to Work I E-Verify I Pay Transparency<br>Company: John Hancock Life Insurance Company (U.S.A.)]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Manager / Assistant Manager, Communications]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Singapore/Manager----Assistant-Manager--Communications_JR25091363?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Singapore<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091363<br>Manulife Singapore is transforming the way we communicate with our people, our customers, and the market. As part of our bold ambition to lead in financial services, we are looking for an exceptional Communications Manager who can craft powerful narratives, translate complex strategies into clear, compelling stories, and inspire confidence across internal and external audiences.<br><br>This is not a “business-as-usual” comms role. You will sit at the heart of Manulife Singapore’s transformation, shaping how we engage our employees, amplify our leaders’ voices, position the company in the media, and drive thought leadership in emerging areas such as longevity, AI, and financial empowerment.<br>If you are passionate about communications, thrive in a fast-paced environment, and are excited by the opportunity to create impact at scale — we want to meet you.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Communications & Thought Leadership<br>Drive Manulife Singapore’s public narrative through media engagement, research-driven storytelling, and creative content campaigns.<br>Position the company and its leadership as trusted voices on longevity, AI, health, and financial confidence through interviews, speaking opportunities, and strategic media outreach.<br>Manage relationships with top-tier media, influence coverage, and deliver messaging that differentiates Manulife from competitors.<br>Partner with senior leaders to prepare for media engagements, speeches, and external events — crafting thought-provoking narratives that connect with diverse audiences.<br>Internal Communications & Employee Engagement<br>Partner closely with the CEO, leadership team, and HR to inspire and align our employees behind our strategy and culture.<br>Lead the storytelling for company-wide moments: townhalls, announcements, awards, employee campaigns, and flagship events.<br>Craft CEO speeches, talking points, and narratives that connect strategy to what matters most to employees and advisors.<br>Build a culture of transparency and connection by developing engaging content for digital channels like Viva Engage, newsletters, videos, and more<br>Strategic Influence & Innovation<br>Use AI-powered tools to enhance your work — from insights mining and content ideation to streamlining reporting and amplifying creative output.<br>Collaborate with regional and global teams to ensure Manulife Singapore’s voice is consistent, differentiated, and future-focused.<br>Champion data-driven communications, measuring impact and iterating campaigns to continuously raise the bar.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>8+ years of experience in communications, marketing, or public relations — ideally in financial services, technology, or high-growth industries.<br>Creative flair in visual storytelling — strong PowerPoint or design capabilities to make content pop.<br>Experience leading large-scale campaigns or change communications initiatives.<br>Familiarity with emerging topics such as AI, longevity and financial well-being<br>A strategic storyteller with exceptional writing and editing skills; able to craft narratives that are sharp, human, and business-aligned.<br>Proven experience working with senior executives, shaping thought leadership, and driving high-stakes narratives.<br>Strong EQ and stakeholder management skills — you build trust quickly and influence effectively.<br>Highly organised, detail-oriented, and able to manage multiple priorities without losing sight of the bigger picture.<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Machine Learning Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Chengdu-Sichuan/Machine-Learning-Engineer_JR25090005?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Chengdu, Sichuan<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 23, 2025 (2 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090005<br>Manulife is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make decisions easier and lives better. Help shape the future you want to see — and discover that better can take you anywhere you want to go.<br><br>JOB DESCRIPTION<br><br>People Leader Role: No<br><br>Responsibilities:<br>Support data operations lifecycle of AA projects - Input into the approach and Owns and manages assigned tasks.<br>Develops and implements ad-hoc and business analytics and reporting on projects of moderate scope<br>Own data pipeline and productionizing<br>Identify and gain access to sources of data with limited assistance from senior team members.<br>Work with internal and external team members to understand the data; present findings to the team.<br>Document the acquired data via standard team templates; present findings to the team<br>Create appropriate tables and DBs<br>Work with internal and external team members to code DS's solution in production system, coach junior team members.<br>Acquire data to measure effectiveness of the solution, present findings to internal and external peers, with guidance from senior team members.<br>Works on problems of moderate scope / complexity where analysis of situations or data requires a review of a variety of factors<br>Ability to generate relevant, actionable insights based on iterative data analysis, translate data-driven output into business language, and to make appropriate recommendations to respective business stakeholders<br>Strong ability to extract, transform and stage data for consumption by the data scientist leveraging data querying tools<br>Provides analysis on datasets of significant complexity.<br>Quickly able to develop enough business insight to connect data sources across multiple diverse and complicated systems.<br>Communicates business analytics of moderate complexity to more senior team members and junior business partners<br>Works closely with subject matter experts to understand data sources.<br>Has intimate understanding of the business value chain and customer lifecycle for the projects they are supporting.<br>Has fundamental understanding of the business as a whole.<br>Curious and asks the right kinds of questions of peers and customers to gain knowledge.<br>Establishes an internal network and leverages the network of more senior data analysts.<br>Provides guidance and mentorship to more junior team members Owns their career development.<br>Takes advantage of available resources to advance their technical and business skills.<br>Understands how their project supports broader business strategy, including the core drivers of business value<br><br>Some ability to construct systematic process to implement analytics insights and solutions, this includes (but not limited to):<br>designing a process with multiple relevant parties with clear specifications of roles and responsibilities<br>identifying required tasks, system / data flow and contingency<br>specifying check-and-balance throughout the process<br>establishing rigorous tracking and closed-loop learning<br>implement such process in a scalable way<br><br>Requirements:<br>Minimum Bachelor’s degree in Math, Computer Science, or Engineering; or Bachelor’s degree with equivalent technical experience<br>Minimum of 2 years of applicable experience Advanced knowledge of programming languages and concepts (g. Java, Sequel, C, SAS, SPSS, R (different modules) or Python)<br>Advanced knowledge of data visualization tools such as Tableau, QlikView, PowerBI<br>Advanced knowledge of data transformation to support BI Reporting Advanced knowledge of common database querying languages such as SQL.<br>Capability of applying a systematic, structured approach to explore / navigate / mine massive amount of data, structured or un-structured, to uncover hidden patterns / insights.<br>Strong working knowledge of relational database models ( data vaulting techniques, rules tables).<br>Advanced knowledge in distributed computing - Hadoop/ NoSQL/unstructured data<br>Basic understanding of different techniques and knowledge of machine learning algorithms.<br>Basic knowledge of AI toolkits.<br>Familiarity with basic statistical tests, distributions, maximum likelihood estimators, statistical modelling techniques (regression, cluster / factor / principle components, decision tree, survival analysis, etc.)<br><br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br><br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Machine Learning Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Chengdu-Sichuan/Machine-Learning-Engineer_JR25090004?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Chengdu, Sichuan<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 23, 2025 (2 days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090004<br>Manulife is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make decisions easier and lives better. Help shape the future you want to see — and discover that better can take you anywhere you want to go.<br><br>JOB DESCRIPTION<br><br>People Leader Role: No<br><br>Responsibilities:<br>Support data operations lifecycle of AA projects - Input into the approach and Owns and manages assigned tasks.<br>Develops and implements ad-hoc and business analytics and reporting on projects of moderate scope<br>Own data pipeline and productionizing<br>Identify and gain access to sources of data with limited assistance from senior team members.<br>Work with internal and external team members to understand the data; present findings to the team.<br>Document the acquired data via standard team templates; present findings to the team<br>Create appropriate tables and DBs<br>Work with internal and external team members to code DS's solution in production system, coach junior team members.<br>Acquire data to measure effectiveness of the solution, present findings to internal and external peers, with guidance from senior team members.<br>Works on problems of moderate scope / complexity where analysis of situations or data requires a review of a variety of factors<br>Ability to generate relevant, actionable insights based on iterative data analysis, translate data-driven output into business language, and to make appropriate recommendations to respective business stakeholders<br>Strong ability to extract, transform and stage data for consumption by the data scientist leveraging data querying tools<br>Provides analysis on datasets of significant complexity.<br>Quickly able to develop enough business insight to connect data sources across multiple diverse and complicated systems.<br>Communicates business analytics of moderate complexity to more senior team members and junior business partners<br>Works closely with subject matter experts to understand data sources.<br>Has intimate understanding of the business value chain and customer lifecycle for the projects they are supporting.<br>Has fundamental understanding of the business as a whole.<br>Curious and asks the right kinds of questions of peers and customers to gain knowledge.<br>Establishes an internal network and leverages the network of more senior data analysts.<br>Provides guidance and mentorship to more junior team members Owns their career development.<br>Takes advantage of available resources to advance their technical and business skills.<br>Understands how their project supports broader business strategy, including the core drivers of business value<br><br>Some ability to construct systematic process to implement analytics insights and solutions, this includes (but not limited to):<br>designing a process with multiple relevant parties with clear specifications of roles and responsibilities<br>identifying required tasks, system / data flow and contingency<br>specifying check-and-balance throughout the process<br>establishing rigorous tracking and closed-loop learning<br>implement such process in a scalable way<br><br>Requirements:<br>Minimum Bachelor’s degree in Math, Computer Science, or Engineering; or Bachelor’s degree with equivalent technical experience<br>Minimum of 2 years of applicable experience Advanced knowledge of programming languages and concepts (g. Java, Sequel, C, SAS, SPSS, R (different modules) or Python)<br>Advanced knowledge of data visualization tools such as Tableau, QlikView, PowerBI<br>Advanced knowledge of data transformation to support BI Reporting Advanced knowledge of common database querying languages such as SQL.<br>Capability of applying a systematic, structured approach to explore / navigate / mine massive amount of data, structured or un-structured, to uncover hidden patterns / insights.<br>Strong working knowledge of relational database models ( data vaulting techniques, rules tables).<br>Advanced knowledge in distributed computing - Hadoop/ NoSQL/unstructured data<br>Basic understanding of different techniques and knowledge of machine learning algorithms.<br>Basic knowledge of AI toolkits.<br>Familiarity with basic statistical tests, distributions, maximum likelihood estimators, statistical modelling techniques (regression, cluster / factor / principle components, decision tree, survival analysis, etc.)<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Assistant Manager, Distribution Compliance (Cebu)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Lapu-Lapu-City/Assistant-Manager--Distribution-Compliance_JR25080062-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Lapu Lapu City,<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25080062<br>We’re looking for an Assistant Manager, Distribution Compliance to join our Integrated Compliance Services (ICS). In this role, you will be responsible in overseeing segment’s day to day operations by setting prioritization of the team's task, provide direction to the team in meeting the level of service. Having strong leadership skills and support manager and tower lead in executing strategic initiatives of ICS.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Leadership<br>Adapts plans and sets priorities to meet service and/or operational challenges<br>Act as point of escalation that uses judgment to identify, troubleshoot, and resolve day-to-day operational problems guided by established standards<br>Provide direction to the team in meeting the level of service (Quality Score, TAT, and timeliness objectives within their area)<br>Providing coaching, motivation, and development of team members<br>Providing training and preparing process documents to new hires <br>Assists the Associate Director with recruitment, workforce management, employment actions, including discipline and termination of employees in accordance with company policy<br>Conducts performance evaluations that are timely and constructive<br>Collaborate with leaders and managers in ensuring talent development of team members and team engagement through execution of ICS initiatives.<br>Risk<br>Ensure all pertinent policies and guidelines of Manulife are being followed by team members and timely completion of Mandatory Compliance Training<br>Ensuring all documents are timely reviewed and placed within a secured repository<br>Stakeholder Management<br>Effectively communicate for any updates and changes to all stakeholders within the segment covered<br>Manage stakeholder expectations through appropriate engagement and timely status reporting on operational highlights<br>Required Qualifications:<br>At least 3 years in a leadership role.<br>2-3 years of experience in distribution compliance, particularly with knowledge of agents and sales processes in insurance or fraud investigations (such as sales misconduct investigation), or experience in regulatory compliance.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Excellent communication skills.<br>Work experience in finance or insurance operations is preferred but not required<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want. <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words. <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Financial Reporting Specialist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Financial-Reporting-Specialist_JR25090690?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 2, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090690<br>The incumbent is responsible for ensuring that portfolio of investments and financial statements prepared for the John Hancock funds are in conformity with SEC requirements. The incumbent is expected to be proficient in various investment products. The position also requires that the incumbent plan and organize work assignments, prioritize training needs of junior staff, train new staff, and assist in preparation of performance reviews. Accountable for the preparation and/ or review of the Portfolio of Investments (POI) section of the Fund Shareholder Reports and Part F of NPORT report. In addition, supervise and assist with scheduling and managing workflows within and outside of Fund Reporting including allocation of departmental resources and training of staff.<br>Responsibilities:<br>Prepare complex fund’s Portfolio of Investments report.<br>Prepare Financial Statements which includes statement of asset and liabilities, statement of operations, changes in net assets, cash flows, financial highlights and notes to financials.<br>Perform reviews of the annual and semi-annual shareholders reports (POI Sections), Forms NQ and N-MFP and other regulatory filings (NCEN and SALT)<br>Assist team members with implementation of complex accounting or regulatory developments.<br>Coordinate and/or perform centralized tasks required in the report preparation and audit processes.<br>Assist with the supervision of less experienced associates to ensure that their assigned work is completed timely, accurately and completely.<br>Ensure that departmental documentation, including policies and procedures and reporting checklists, are accurate and current.<br>Manage and/or participate in the departmental special projects and other duties as assigned.<br>Identify and implement improvement opportunities and stream-line end-to-end process for Fund Reporting using Alteryx.<br>Qualifications: <br>Advanced knowledge of mutual fund industry including the accounting for mutual funds.<br>University degree in accounting, finance or economics and CPA, CFA, CISI or CAT passer preferred.<br>Strong understanding of Investment theory and terminology, as well as financial accounting concepts. This may be derived from academic study or related work experience.<br>Strong understanding of US GAAP and SEC regulations governing financial reporting and accounting.<br>Working knowledge of MS Excel, Macros (e.g. Visual Basic); fund reporting tool (e.g. FundSuite ARC).<br>2 years of directly related fund reporting experience required.<br>When you join our team:<br>• We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>• We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>• As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Financial Senior Specialist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Financial-Senior-Specialist_JR25081047?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>Lapu Lapu City,<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25081047<br>Reporting directly to Asia Finance Shared Service, Team Leader, the Finance Senior Specialist is primarily accountable for general accounting and reporting through timely and accurate service delivery.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>The job holder is responsible to learn, coordinate and work closely with business unit in migrating accounting and finance processes which includes process documentation – creating comprehensive step-by-step procedure of each processes learned.<br>Assist the leader and the project team in identifying processes that can be migrated in MBPS. Assess based on migration criteria and provide feedback and inputs as necessary.<br>Assist the leader in providing updates in the migration.<br>Serve as the contact person of the project team in getting regular updates, challenges encountered, results monitoring of the parallel run.<br>Learn the processes to be migrated and provide timely process documentation following the standard MBPS format as aligned with the Control Tower.<br>Serve as the business unit point of contact for any process issues or task specific queries. <br>The job holder is responsible to train junior team members of the processes already migrated. Ensure complete transfer of knowledge through theoretical training, reverse shadowing, and guide the team members from parallel run to go-live.<br>Serve as the go-to person of the specific location in terms of the knowledge of the processes.<br>Create training plan in case of task re-allocation.<br>Provide timely feedback on team members for the perusal of the leader.<br>Provide coaching and additional training for items that needs further clarification prior to raising to the BU.<br>The job holder will be given processes that will be subject to his/her review on top of his/her daily, monthly production work. It will part of her responsibility to monitor junior team members work, ensure error-free submission and be accountable for the processes subject to his/her review.<br>Ensure that all processes/deliverables for the day have undergone internal review process prior to BU submission.<br>Follow the quality checklist as documented during migration. Ensure that the preparer adhere to the signed of process documentation.<br>Assist the leader in providing root cause analysis and action items for incidents encountered during the month.<br>Operations – finance operations transactional in nature but has financial impact (e.g. Invoicing, Credit Card Refund, Daily Matching of Premium) <br>Accounting Operations – responsible in preparing, uploading of Journal Entry to facilitate month-end closing activities. Reconciliation of accounts and balance sheet items for regulatory requirements <br>Reconciliation - performs reconciliation such as Bank Reconciliation, Intercompany Reconciliation and System reconciliation to ensure completeness and correctness of financial information for the month.<br>Management Reporting – to support needs of different internal or external parties.<br>Propose automation for tasks assigned and  <br>Support junior members on their automation initiatives. <br>Coordinate with Business Developers on status of automation projects. <br>Lead User Acceptance Testing and report result to Team Leader. <br><br>Required Qualifications:<br>Bachelor’s degree in accounting or finance or any related field; CPA preferred.<br>Minimum of 5 years of related work experience with progressive responsibility within accounting and management reporting field at least 3 of which is with an international organization or Shared Service Center.<br>Hybrid Work Arrangement: Amenability and readiness to work onsite and from home anytime (dependent on business need AND/OR current external environment/situation) and must be willing to work on a day shift schedule<br>Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills. <br>Ability to work in an ambiguous environment and adapt to change while managing time and workload with aggressive timelines. <br>Preferably with process migration background<br>Extensive experience in account analysis and reconciliation<br>Intermediate to Advanced knowledge of Excel (i.e. mastery of excel formulas and pivot tables is a must; VBA is a plus). Proficient in MS Office suite including Outlook, Word, Power Point.<br>Willing to work on dayshift and overtime may be required to meet business deadlines. <br>Strong interpersonal and English (written and verbal) communication skills.<br>Ability to work independently, self-motivated, resourceful, and a team-player.<br>When you join our team:<br> We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br> We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br> As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Manager/ Manager, Underwriting]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Hong-Kong/Senior-Manager--Manager--Underwriting_JR25091357-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Hong Kong<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091357<br>We’re looking for a driven and strategic professional to join our team as a Senior Manager or Manager in Underwriting.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Develop and deliver tailored training sessions for distribution channels, focusing on risk assessment and underwriting knowledge.<br>Coordinate and lead targeted sessions for the H&P Ambassador Program and digital tools training.<br>Serve as a primary point of contact for the agency channel, addressing Underwriting inquiries.<br>Facilitate regular and impactful communication with distribution channels to ensure their needs are met effectively.<br>Collaborate with internal teams to provide timely and accurate support to drive channel growth.<br>Manage multiple demands from distribution channels while maintaining high standards of service.<br>Qualifications:<br>Degree or equivalent business qualifications<br>LOMA qualification preferred<br>Proven experience in distribution channel support or a related field.<br>Strong understanding of risk assessment and financial products.<br>Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.<br>Ability to manage multiple tasks efficiently in a fast-paced environment.<br>Problem-solving skills to address inquiries and resolve issues promptly.<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Compliance Supervisory Associate, Wealth Operations]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Supervision-Associate_JR25061177?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: November 13, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25061177<br>The Wealth Operations – Compliance Supervisory Associate is a pivotal role within our updated supervision structure, dedicated primarily to supporting the supervision of financial advisors at Manulife Wealth. This position focuses on essential non-licensed tasks that help maintain regulatory compliance and support the Tier 1 Supervision Team. Reporting directly to the National Director Field Supervision, the Supervision Associate is instrumental in ensuring that advisors adhere to regulatory requirements, thereby protecting the interests of both the firm and its clients.<br>As a Compliance Supervisory Associate, you will be responsible for executing a variety of tasks that facilitate the supervision process. Your duties will include processing updates to client information, managing approvals for various account-related activities, analysis managed account data for quarterly meetings and supporting supervision control processes. Additionally, you will assist in tracking high-level audit responses and preparing for branch visits, thereby contributing to a comprehensive compliance framework that supports the firm’s regulatory commitments.<br>Your role requires strong organizational skills and the ability to collaborate effectively with various departments. By maintaining detailed records and supporting operational initiatives, you will enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of our compliance operations, ensuring a balance between excellent service and rigorous adherence to supervision requirements. This role works closely with licensed Supervision staff that may need to be a secondary approver of your work.<br> Position Responsibilities:<br>Advisor Supervision & Branch Reviews<br>Outside activity review for Supervision Manager approvals<br>Shared premise review sent for secondary approval by Supervision Manager<br>Relocation template approvals<br>Associate advisor delegation letters<br>Collect, track and report on audit response and article collections for audits<br>Collect pre-work and prepare reporting for Advisor Supervision Manager Branch Visits<br>Collection and analysis of managed account data<br>Account /Trade Reviews<br>Multiple non-material account reviews, including:<br>Update to non-material client updates<br>Name and address updates, including hold-mail requests<br>Foreign wires<br>Non-qualified security<br>Donations<br>Advisor code changes<br>Manual account pre-reviews<br>Restriction requests<br>Banking and systematic event approvals<br>Transfer approvals<br>POS failure inquiries<br>Field Supervision Controls<br>Provide reporting on effectiveness and efficiency of account and trade supervision<br>Manage restriction control process for outdated KYC, foreign accounts, IA code changes etc<br>Execute release testing<br>Additional Accountabilities<br>Management of the field supervision inbox<br>Submission of sanction fines to commission<br>Reimbursement review and submission to commission<br>Preliminary AML flag analysis<br>Branch Visit data collection to support this critical function<br>Hard and soft skills<br>Draft job aids and policy/process documents, including Wealth Guide articles<br>Updating and tracking:<br>Compliance courses<br>AML training<br>Proofpoint completions and remediation actions<br>Other responsibilities as advisors join or depart the firm<br>Other responsibilities required to support field supervision<br> Qualifications and Skills: <br>Professional background in the financial services industry preferably with a Canadian Investment Regulatory Organization (CIRO) Dealer<br>Knowledge of the FCC System is an asset<br>Knowledge of Portfolio Aid 360 is an asset<br>Microsoft tools such as power BI, sharepoint and excel is necessary<br>Organizational and prioritization skills to be able to work in a multitasking environment<br>A capacity to engage constructively and respectfully with individuals at all levels of the organization, and an ability to achieve high-quality outcomes<br>Highly detailed oriented<br>Can manage the balance between servicing and supporting advisors while ensuring we follow supervision requirements<br>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills and sound professional judgment <br>Ability to manage ambiguity<br>French language skills would be a bonus but not mandatory<br> When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Analyst, Agency Compensation]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Kuala-Lumpur-Wilayah-Persekutuan-Kuala-Lumpur/Analyst--Agency-Compensation_JR25091446?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Kuala Lumpur, Wilayah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091446<br>The Opportunity <br>This position is responsible for managing payments to the Agency and Partnership channels, including commissions, bonuses, financing schemes, and incentives. The role ensures timely and accurate compensation processing for Tied Agency, ALC Agency, and Partnership Channel. It also involves conducting moderately complex managerial analysis and reporting, as well as maintaining and updating records in the PICS system and other platforms to support business growth.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Action commission related inquiries from internal departments including the Contact Center and Distribution by promptly and accurately responding<br>Research and resolve commission inquiries by applying knowledge to resolve complex inquiries and performing reconciliation of payments made<br>Complete Commission Run Related Tasks as per set schedule, which includes ensuring all advisors are compensated for bank products<br>Complete monthly balancing for Finance<br>Prepare monthly Value At Risk (VaR) monitoring report to Local Line1B team for further action. Leverage of Power BI to automate the report for ease of reporting and efficiency. Monitor the VaR for accuracy and facilitate enquiry from Line1B.<br>Prepare monthly IR validation and payout<br>Maintain the integrity of commission records fed from the Compensation Database to Distribution (importing/exporting, reviewing invalid sales rep codes, processing adjustments and corrections, reviewing reject reports) as well as doing the reconciliation<br>Administer complex transfers of business between advisors (including supporting staff who are completing noncomplex transfers)<br>Contribute to department targets by ensuring all inquiries/tasks are answered as per Service Level Agreements<br>Report issues, process gaps and opportunities to Manager when identified to enhance service levels and the customer experience<br>Keep current on knowledge of products and commission schedule updates<br>Support projects as they relate to Commissions<br>Required Qualifications:<br>Bachelor’s degree in Accounting ,Finance, Mathematic, Actuarial or equivalent<br>Fresh Graduate or equivalent work experience<br>Good knowledge of Excel<br>Strong analytical and decision making ability<br>Positive attitude and strong desire to achieve<br>Ability to work in a dynamic, high-paced environment independently and as part of a team<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Assistant Supervisor Policy Benefit]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Labuan/Assistant-Supervisor-Policy-Benefit_JR25091460?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Labuan<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091460<br>The Opportunity <br>Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You’ve come to the right place. We’re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we’d like to hear from you<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Timely process MILL workbasket items as per the agreed TAT. Process/ approve policy administration and benefits request: Policy changes with Financial and non-financial, Cash Surrender, Policy Loan and Withdrawal.<br>Monitoring Daily Productivity, achieve individual KPI - a minimum 100%.<br>Involve, plan, brainstorm and perform UAT and projects (at least 30% of the time).<br>Manage MILL Policy Servicing emails, ensure the documents submission and enquiries are handle timely and settle within TAT.<br>Open and stamp incoming mails (if any). Data entry on all documents received, record in department Share Point.<br>Prepare reports and update SOPs as and when changes occur or changes in regulations.<br>Check then decide close Bridger alerts or escalate alert to Compliance team timely.<br>Ensure Annual statement, quarterly statement and Servicing correspondence deliver to customers, bankers/ financial advisers timely.<br>Prepare documents for filing/storage (in-house filing and arranging storage process with Crown Record Management).<br>Prepare Payment Authorization Form for payments.<br>Other administrative duties and assigned duties as and when required by the HOD.<br>Required Qualifications: <br>Fresh graduate with University Degree in any discipline, or<br>At least one year’s experience in Insurance Industry, preferably in Policy Servicing or Life Insurance<br>Able to work long hours, public holidays and weekends as required<br>Familiarity with working with CAS systems and Microsoft Office.<br>Able to plan and organize to ensure all tasks are carried out effectively and efficiently<br>Able to work independently<br>Good interpersonal skills.<br>Good working attitude and discipline.<br>Initiative, self-motivated, customer focused and able to work as a team.<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: IT Operations & Data Support Coordinator]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Makati-City/IT-Operations---Data-Support-Coordinator_JR25091513?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Makati City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091513<br>At Manulife, we are committed to delivering exceptional solutions and services to our clients. We are seeking a skilled and motivated Analyst to join our team. This role will support the ongoing development and optimization of our data management and contract management processes. If you are passionate about data integrity, process improvement, and collaborating with cross-functional teams, we want to hear from you!<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Contract & Procurement Support<br>Help submit contract requests and purchase orders using tools like Ivalua and SNOW.<br>Work with internal teams (Procurement, Finance, Legal, Risk) to support contract reviews and approvals.<br>Assist with vendor quotes and basic negotiations.<br>Support invoice submissions and ensure correct approvals are in place.<br>Maintain simple reports for software contracts and help with post-contract activities like audits.<br>Jira Data Support<br>Help IT teams keep Jira data clean and organized.<br>Run basic data checks and flag any issues.<br>Share reminders and tips with teams to improve data quality.<br>Suggest improvements to make data management easier.<br>Workforce Coordination<br>Support onboarding and offboarding processes for IT staff.<br>Help keep workforce data accurate and up to date.<br>Assist with routine audits and collaborate with other teams to improve processes.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>At least 1-3 years of experience<br>Strong attention to detail and willingness to learn.<br>Good communication and organizational skills.<br>Working knowledge of tools like Excel and the Microsoft Office suite<br>A collaborative mindset and interest in IT operations or data support.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Exposure to procurement or contract processes.<br>Experience working with data or reporting tools.<br>Interest in improving team workflows and systems.<br>When you join our team: <br>• We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>• We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>• As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: AML/KYC Compliance Specialist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/AML-KYC-Compliance-Specialist_JR25091469?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: November 13, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091469<br>This a pivotal role within our updated supervision structure, dedicated primarily to supporting the supervision of financial advisors at Manulife Wealth. This position focuses on essential non-licensed tasks that help maintain regulatory compliance and support the Tier 1 Supervision Team. Reporting directly to the National Director Field Supervision, the Supervision Associate is instrumental in ensuring that advisors adhere to regulatory requirements, thereby protecting the interests of both the firm and its clients.<br>In this role, you will be responsible for executing a variety of tasks that facilitate the supervision process. Your duties will include processing updates to client information, managing approvals for various account-related activities, analysis managed account data for quarterly meetings and supporting supervision control processes. Additionally, you will assist in tracking high-level audit responses and preparing for branch visits, thereby contributing to a comprehensive compliance framework that supports the firm’s regulatory commitments.<br>Your role requires strong organizational skills and the ability to collaborate effectively with various departments. By maintaining detailed records and supporting operational initiatives, you will enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of our compliance operations, ensuring a balance between excellent service and rigorous adherence to supervision requirements. This role works closely with licensed Supervision staff that may need to be a secondary approver of your work.<br> Position Responsibilities:<br>Advisor Supervision & Branch Reviews<br>Outside activity review for Supervision Manager approvals<br>Shared premise review sent for secondary approval by Supervision Manager<br>Relocation template approvals<br>Associate advisor delegation letters<br>Collect, track and report on audit response and article collections for audits<br>Collect pre-work and prepare reporting for Advisor Supervision Manager Branch Visits<br>Collection and analysis of managed account data<br>Account /Trade Reviews<br>Multiple non-material account reviews, including:<br>Update to non-material client updates<br>Name and address updates, including hold-mail requests<br>Foreign wires<br>Non-qualified security<br>Donations<br>Advisor code changes<br>Manual account pre-reviews<br>Restriction requests<br>Banking and systematic event approvals<br>Transfer approvals<br>POS failure inquiries<br>Field Supervision Controls<br>Provide reporting on effectiveness and efficiency of account and trade supervision<br>Manage restriction control process for outdated KYC, foreign accounts, IA code changes etc<br>Execute release testing<br>Additional Accountabilities<br>Management of the field supervision inbox<br>Submission of sanction fines to commission<br>Reimbursement review and submission to commission<br>Preliminary AML flag analysis<br>Branch Visit data collection to support this critical function<br>Hard and soft skills<br>Draft job aids and policy/process documents, including Wealth Guide articles<br>Updating and tracking:<br>Compliance courses<br>AML training<br>Proofpoint completions and remediation actions<br>Other responsibilities as advisors join or depart the firm<br>Other responsibilities required to support field supervision<br> Qualifications and Skills: <br>Professional background in the financial services industry <br>Microsoft tools such as power BI, sharepoint and excel is necessary<br>Organizational and prioritization skills to be able to work in a multitasking environment<br>A capacity to engage constructively and respectfully with individuals at all levels of the organization, and an ability to achieve high-quality outcomes<br>Highly detailed oriented<br>Can manage the balance between servicing and supporting advisors while ensuring we follow supervision requirements<br>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills and sound professional judgment <br>Ability to manage ambiguity<br> When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Insurance Specialist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Kandal/Senior-Insurance-Specialist_JR25091436-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Kandal<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: November 1, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091436<br>Job Posting Description<br>The Insurance Specialist is responsible for providing life insurance solutions to Bank's clients. He/she will work in coordination with branch sales and service teams; thus, we are looking for a dynamic individual, who has an independent mindset and the drive to succeed. <br>Position Responsibilities:  <br>• Promote and provide tailored life insurance solutions to address client's protection, and long-term saving needs  <br>• Build and maintain strong client relationships to support long-term financial planning. <br>• Generate leads through networking, referrals, and cold calling <br>• Stay updated on industry trends, product offerings, and regulatory changes <br>• Perform other tasks as required. <br>Required Qualifications:  <br>• Bachelor's/ College Degree holder <br>• Work experience in bancassurance sales is highly preferred but those with sales and customer service experience are also encouraged to apply  <br>• Good at communication, interpersonal, and client relationship skills <br>• Self-driven, commitment and highly motivated  <br>Preferred Qualifications:  <br>• Ability to analyze client needs and recommend suitable solutions <br>• Customer service orientation with problem-solving ability. <br>• A capacity for constant learning from both success and failure <br>• Open to change and continuous improvement <br>When you join our team:  <br>• We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.  <br>• We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.  <br>• As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Fixed Income and Derivatives Trader]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Singapore/Fixed-Income-and-Derivatives-Trader_JR25091506-1?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Singapore<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: November 30, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091506<br>This role offers an exciting opportunity to become an integral part of Manulife's Asia General Account Investments team, contributing to the company's mission by supporting the growth of its investment portfolio. As a Fixed Income and Derivatives Trader, you will play a key role in executing trades, monitoring risk exposures, and developing innovative financial instruments to enhance Manulife's investment and risk management capabilities. This position provides a dynamic environment where you can make real-time business decisions, collaborate with various internal stakeholders, and directly impact the company's success.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Execute fixed income and derivatives trades for Asia General Account Investments.<br>Monitor and rebalance the Variable Annuity Hedging (VAH) program.<br>Manage counterparty onboarding and assess broker capabilities.<br>Collaborate with internal stakeholders to address investment and risk management challenges.<br>Analyze market trends and provide market intelligence to support business objectives.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>1-3 years of experience in a financial services environment.<br>University degree in a quantitative discipline (e.g., engineering, math, science, economics, or finance).<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Experience working with derivatives products.<br>Strong interpersonal and communication skills.<br>Ability to think strategically and develop proactive solutions.<br>Programming ability.<br>Project management experience.<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Talent Acquisition Consultant]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Chengdu-Sichuan/Talent-Acquisition-Consultant_JR25071213?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Chengdu, Sichuan<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 21, 2025 (14 hours left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25071213<br>Manulife is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make decisions easier and lives better. Help shape the future you want to see — and discover that better can take you anywhere you want to go.<br><br>JOB DESCRIPTION<br><br>People Leader Role: No<br><br>This position partners with lines of business and functional areas to provide strategic recruiting services to ensure that the company’s recruiting programs maximize visibility and result in high quality hires.<br><br>Key Responsibilities:<br>Partner with lines of business and functional areas to provide strategic recruiting services to ensure that the company’s recruiting programs maximize visibility and result in high quality hires<br>Assess candidates using behavioral based interviewing to ensure top quality talent is selected<br>Coach managers on the recruiting process, interview techniques, and selection criteria<br>Stay current on recruitment trends by maintaining and enhancing a network of contacts in the industry, participating in industry events and professional associations<br>Partner with management in the proactive sourcing of talent for critical skill areas to build a talent pipeline<br>Create and execute strategic sourcing plans to attract top talent, both passive and active<br>Effectively utilize Affinity groups to attract targeted talent groups to MANULIFE<br>Internally market our services to employees and managers, promoting our value add and expertise<br>Drive the candidate selection process and ensure managers have the tools needed to select the most qualified candidate<br>Ensure all staffing processes are fair and equitable and comply with all relevant government regulations<br>Manage and/or participate in projects as needed<br>Other duties as assigned<br><br>Job Requirements:<br>BS/BA, proficient in English (IELTS 6.0 or equivalent level) .<br>Hands-on experience in Office Suite, Workday.<br>Analytical and open-minded, with a commitment to continuous learning and development <br>5-7 years of recruiting experience with a proven track record in successfully filling technology-focused roles, such as Cloud specialists, UI/UX designers, and Data Scientists.<br>Experience using alternative sourcing methods, with a focus on social media and networking tools.<br>Demonstrated success in taking a consultative approach with internal and external clients while providing business solutions.<br>Organized and detail oriented with a pro-active approach.<br>Demonstrated ability to navigate an environment with multiple and shifting priorities with ease.<br>Customer centric attitude coupled with a sense of urgency.<br>Strong knowledge of labor market and industry trends.<br>Strong knowledge of business unit products, drivers, and strategies.<br>Exceptional communication skills- crisp and articulate verbal skills in addition to effective written communication required.<br>Well networked.<br><br>Decision Authorities:<br>Provide salary recommendations to hiring managers based on internal and external market data and candidate salary expectations.<br>Recommend sourcing strategies and identify proper channels and messages to find targeted sources of high-quality candidates.<br><br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br><br>This job description is not a comprehensive listing of all job duties required for this role. We reserve the right to change these duties or assign additional duties at any time with or without notice<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Senior Data Scientist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Chengdu-Sichuan/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR25090003?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Chengdu, Sichuan<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: September 21, 2025 (14 hours left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090003<br>Manulife is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make decisions easier and lives better. Help shape the future you want to see — and discover that better can take you anywhere you want to go.<br><br>Responsibilities:<br>Develops and implements analytics enabled solutions to improve business process, to generate insights, support business goals and strategy development<br>Owns and delivers projects of diverse scope.<br>Oversees the work of more junior data scientists.<br>Works on problems of diverse scope / complexity where analysis of situations or data requires an in-depth evaluation of a variety of factors<br>Strong ability to generate relevant, actionable insights based on iterative data analysis, translate data-driven output into business language, and to make appropriate recommendations to respective business stakeholders<br>Independently provides analysis on datasets of significant complexity.<br>Quickly able to develop enough business insight to connect data sources across multiple diverse and complicated systems.<br>Recommends implementable solutions to (or in collaboration with) business partners.<br>Considers change management in all aspects of their work.<br>Supports more junior data scientists with Change Management.<br>Has intimate understanding of the business value chain and customer lifecycle for a line of business or more.<br>Has fundamental understanding of the business as a whole, and has started to build a network of people for ideation, info sharing, knowledge.<br>Understands the corporate climate and culture Strong knowledge of the business<br>Engages in ongoing discussions and moves others towards a position, appealing to their needs and interests to gain acceptance<br>Maintains a strong internal network, begins to network with more senior stakeholders within the organization.<br>Begins to develop an external network and develop their own brand, particular in their own practice area.<br>Actively involved in recruitment of data science professionals (campus etc.0<br>Shares ideas with others, leads brainstorming sessions.<br>Contributes to solutions outside immediate area of expertise.<br>Actively seeks out coaching and incorporates feedback into their work.<br>Provides guidance and mentorship to more junior data scientists.<br>Promotes best practices within the team.<br>Shares technical expertise with others.<br>Owns their career development.<br>Takes advantage of available resources to advance their technical and business skills.<br>Understands how their project supports broader business strategy, including the core drivers of business value.<br>Able to prepare a business case on the benefits of their assigned work.<br>Incorporates lessons learned throughout the business into their work.<br>Engages with global counterparts to share learnings.<br><br>Strong ability to construct systematic process to implement analytics insights and solutions, this includes (but not limited to):<br>designing a process with multiple relevant parties with clear specifications of roles and responsibilities<br>identifying required tasks, system / data flow and contingency<br>specifying check-and-balance throughout the process<br>establishing rigorous tracking and closed-loop learning<br>implement such process in a scalable way<br><br>Requirements:<br>Advanced degree in Statistics, Math, Computer Science, or Engineering; or Bachelor’s degree with equivalent technical experience<br>Minimum of 5 years of applicable experience Advanced knowledge of programming languages and concepts ( SAS, SPSS, R (different modules) or Python)<br>Expert in basic and advanced statistical tests, distributions, maximum likelihood estimators, statistical modelling techniques (regression, cluster / factor / principle components, decision tree, survival analysis, etc.<br>Advanced knowledge of different techniques and knowledge of machine learning algorithms.<br>Basic knowledge of AI toolkits.<br>Expert in data visualization tools such as Tableau, QlikView, open source data visualization libraries - ggplot and d3.js<br>Advanced knowledge of common database querying languages such as SQL.<br>Capability of applying a systematic, structured approach to explore / navigate / mine massive amount of data, structured or un-structured, to uncover hidden patterns / insights.<br>Strong working knowledge of relational database models (data vaulting techniques, rules tables).<br> When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Financial Analyst, Private Assets Financial Reporting]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Financial-Analyst--Private-Assets-Financial-Reporting_JR25090247?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: November 24, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090247<br>We’re looking for a Financial Analyst to join our Private Assets Financial Reporting team at MBPS. In this role, you are expected to assist, prepare, and provide support on all financial accounting, reporting, analysis and advisory aspects of Private Asset classes including Real Estate, Fixed Income and Infrastructure. The person will also be accountable for delivering on financial reporting and analysis mandate as outlined below for various funds and separately managed accounts for the asset classes noted above. All the responsibilities noted below will have to be executed in collaboration and remote supervision of team in North America.<br>Have the skills and knowledge for the job? Learn more about the opening below!<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>Preparation of monthly and quarterly financial reporting packages in collaboration with the Team in North America.<br>Assist in preparation of financial statements and disclosures in compliance with both under IFRS and US GAAP; Knowledge of US GAAP is not necessary and clear instructions will be provided from the team in North America.<br>Assist in review and checking accuracy and completeness of information provided by third party Fund Administrators and internal operations and reporting teams.<br>Coordination and supporting the Senior Financial Analysts, Managers and Directors with the external audit process.<br>Completing monthly and quarterly reports provided to internal stakeholders and senior management teams reporting AUM, Net Asset Values, Returns<br>Preparation and analysis of financial and non-financial information included in financial statements, Investment management reports, consultant questionnaires and other investor communications for the funds and separately managed accounts.<br>Assist Preparation of cash flows and distribution models and supporting analyses.<br>Assist in developing fund level expense budgets and prepare cash flows and distribution models based on property level forecast. Analyze and develop forward looking analyses and projections as required by Director & Manager of Financial Reporting as well as Portfolio Management team.<br>Analyze and monitor Fund and REIT level expense budget to actual expenses.<br>Assist in preparation of Board of Directors reporting package on a quarterly basis for various funds.<br>Represent finance on various working groups and committees within Finance and the Asset Management business.<br>Support the execution of the acquisitions and financing transactions of various Real Estate Portfolios.<br>Assist with the Yardi conversion process and collaborate with Real Estate Transformation team.<br>Strong focus on collaboration and relationships with various internal and external stakeholders<br>Assist with ad-hoc projects and new initiatives within the department.<br>Qualifications:<br>Bachelor’s degree in Accountancy or Finance, preferred;<br>Professional Accounting Designation (CPA, CA or equivalent) is a plus;<br>A minimum of 2 years of related business experience either with the Accounting Firms or in External Financial Reporting / FP&A function of Real Estate Investment Trusts or Real Estate Operating Companies (REOCs) and / or other similar roles with Alternative Asset Management Companies;<br>Amenability and readiness to work onsite for at least 3x a week and from home 2x a week. Must be willing to work mid-shift (3PM-12PM Manila time);<br>Minimum Skills to Hire/Must Haves:<br>Strong attention to detail and aptitude to learn<br>Ability to multi-task, effectively prioritize, work under tight timelines and manage multiple stakeholders;<br>Well-organized and with high level of energy and initiative to perform in a fast paced and challenging environment<br>Excellent verbal and written communication skills with high degree of confidence.<br>Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills<br>Ability to work independently and establish priorities to meet deadlines<br>Advanced level of proficiency in MS Excel and other MS office tools (e.g. Word and PowerPoint to develop reports, documents and presentations)<br>Knowledgeable in IFRS and/or US GAAP<br>Experience with Yardi or Workiva system is an asset<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Compliance Administrator Assistant]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Compliance-Administrator-Assistant_JR25081593?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 27, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25081593<br>We're looking for a Compliance Administrator Assistant to join our ICS team at MBPS. In this role, you will support the ICS Deputy Head and the ASC Leadership team by coordinating reporting activities, preparing financial statements, and managing bookkeeping tasks. It also involves supporting ICS processes like KYC and EDD, overseeing expenditures and procurement, managing documentation, and conducting onsite branch reviews.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>This role involves reporting to the ICS Deputy Head and supporting the Asia Segment Compliance (ASC) Leadership team by coordinating reporting exercises and providing accurate reports to ASC and the Global Compliance Office.<br>Prepare financial statements, handle finance invoices and billings, manage bookkeeping tasks for ASC, and ensure accurate journaling of expenses and charges.<br>Manage corporate records, monitor expenditures according to internal control procedures, report on budget status, and undertake procurement of goods and services following company rules.<br>Provide support for ICS processes such as conducting due diligence.<br>Manage the integrity of tracking spreadsheets, conduct follow-ups on outstanding items, assist with quality control processes, and create regular and ad-hoc reports for management.<br>Oversee program documentation control, update documents with approved changes, implement version control, provide recommendations for improvements, and conduct onsite reviews of branches as needed.<br>Required Qualifications: <br>Open for fresh graduates, though preference will be given to candidates with at least one year of relevant work experience in a professional setting.<br>A bachelor's degree in any field is required.<br>Demonstrates exceptional attention to detail, resourcefulness, and adaptability to changing environments and requirements.<br>Preferred Qualifications: <br>Proficient in MS Office Suite of products including MS Word, Excel and Power Point, etc;Strong written and verbal communication skills.<br>Strong organizational and comprehension abilities.<br>A Certified Public Accountant (CPA) designation is highly desirable.<br>Knowledge and experience in administrative; financial accounting and full range of office support work, with a high level of sustained performance.<br>Proven experience in finance, bookkeeping, and auditing.<br>When you join our team: <br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want. <br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words. <br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see. <br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Account Coordinator]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Makati-City/Account-Coordinator_JR25091504?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Makati City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091504<br>Reporting to the Media Hub Director, the Account Coordinator will play a vital role in supporting the execution of integrated marketing campaigns that connect meaningfully with target audiences. This role is focused on the coordination and management of various tasks related to campaign execution, performance tracking, and client communication. You will collaborate with internal teams to ensure projects are delivered on time and align with client objectives.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Support the media hub team in the execution of integrated marketing strategies for clients, ensuring smooth coordination of all campaign elements.<br>Assist in preparing and maintaining project timelines, ensuring deliverables are met in accordance with client schedules and expectations.<br>Collaborate with media buyers and analysts to track campaign performance, compiling data to generate insightful reports for internal and client review.<br>Coordinate communication between internal stakeholders and clients, providing updates on project status and facilitating feedback.<br>Help organize meetings, create agendas, and ensure actionable items are documented and followed up on for effective project management.<br>Conduct research and gather insights to inform marketing strategies, optimizing campaign effectiveness and client satisfaction.<br>Maintain organized records of campaign performance metrics and documentation to support efficient workflows and reporting processes.<br>Assist in the preparation of client presentations and proposals, ensuring materials are polished and aligned with client branding and objectives.<br>Monitor industry trends and competitor activities to provide insights that could influence client campaigns and strategies.<br>Support the development of creative briefs and other project documentation to guide internal teams in the execution of client campaigns.<br>Participate in brainstorming sessions and contribute ideas for innovative marketing solutions that align with client goals.<br>Manage internal and external calendars for scheduling meetings and ensuring all stakeholders are informed of key dates and deliverables.<br>Assist in preparing for and participating in client meetings, including taking detailed notes and ensuring follow-up communication is timely and clear.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>Bachelor’s degree in Marketing, Advertising, Business, or a related field.<br>1-2 years of experience in a marketing, advertising, or agency environment (internships and entry-level experience are welcomed).<br>Strong organizational skills with the ability to manage multiple tasks and prioritize effectively in a fast-paced environment.<br>Excellent written and verbal communication skills; comfortable collaborating with teammates and clients.<br>Familiarity with digital marketing channels and tools, including social media, search engine marketing, and basic reporting platforms.<br>Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite (Excel, PowerPoint, Word) and basic project management tools (e.g., Asana, Trello).<br>Enthusiastic, eager to learn, and able to work collaboratively in a team-oriented setting.<br>Understanding of media performance measurement concepts and an analytical mindset is a plus.<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Business Intelligence Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Makati-City/Business-Intelligence-Analyst_JR25091503?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Makati City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091503<br>We are seeking a skilled BI Analyst to join our team in Technology Business Operations (TBO), part of the Canadian Segment IT team. The successful candidate will deliver data analysis and visualization to address IT, business, and operational challenges. This role involves designing and conducting analyses to resolve operational and process issues, collecting and interpreting data to generate reports on project health and trends, and partnering with stakeholders to define the scope and technical requirements.<br>Position Responsibilities:<br>Develop and improve dashboards using PowerBI and other reporting tools, adhering to UI/UX best practices.<br>Support in maintaining business intelligence tools and ensuring compliance with data governance.<br>Support the transformation of planning, workforce, portfolio, and governance for Value Streams and squads.<br>Contribute to the governance and strategic reporting of portfolio project management.<br>Facilitate meetings and manage stakeholder perspectives to achieve optimal solutions.<br>Engage in data and process modeling/design, conduct data audits, and provide support for workforce and portfolio management.<br>Collaborate with the architecture and data technical teams to produce actionable insights.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>At least 3-5 years of experience in the following:<br>Proven experience in data analysis and visualization.<br>Proficiency in PowerBI, Microsoft Excel and other reporting tools.<br>Strong understanding of UI/UX best practices.<br>Experience in data governance and compliance.<br>Excellent communication, problem-solving and stakeholder management skills.<br>Ability to conduct data audits and engage in data and process modeling/design.<br>Experience in supporting workforce and portfolio management.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Programming skills and/or cloud platform experience (i.e. Azure)<br>Industry knowledge: Understanding of the financial services industry, particularly in IT and business operations.<br>AI applications in business intelligence<br>When you join our team:<br>• We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>• We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>• As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Derivatives Operation Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Quezon-City/Derivatives-Operation-Analyst_JR25090293?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Quezon City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: October 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25090293<br>We are seeking a meticulous and detail-oriented Derivatives Operation Analyst to join our team. The successful candidate will be responsible for ensuring the accuracy and integrity of the trade data and the overall trade lifecycle. This role is critical in maintaining operational efficiency and compliance with regulatory standards.<br> Position Responsibilities:<br>Issue collateral margin calls, substitutions and general collateral oversight/margin management for Futures, OTC, and Cleared products<br>Develop and manage working relationships with clearing broker back-office counterparts.<br>Process internal ad hoc requests from various groups in a timely and efficient manner<br>Update or create new process documents for all tasks relevant to the position and maintain internal database of all process documents<br>Propose improvements to current processes that will increase the efficiency and effectiveness of the group<br>Contribute to the gathering of data for quarterly metrics reporting to senior management<br>Complete daily, weekly, monthly, quarterly, and year-end reporting duties in a timely manner<br>Contribute to the capacity and depth of Global Derivatives Services in order to respond to the organization’s current and future derivative demands.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>College / University graduate (preferably Math, Business, Finance or related fields) with minimum 2 to 3 years' work experience in Banking, Finance and/or Investments field<br>Basic knowledge of financial markets and the language and terminology used in Investment Management<br>Hybrid Work Arrangement: Amenability and readiness to work onsite and from home anytime (dependent on business need AND/OR current external environment/situation) and must be willing to work on a day shift schedule<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Possesses an understanding of the pre-trade and post trade process including trade allocation, matching, confirmation, and reconciliation for financial products<br>Familiarity with MS Office suite and knowledgeable of MS office.<br>Solid organizational skills and a high degree of professionalism combined with the ability to readily adapt to rapidly changing environments and deal with competing priorities.<br>Demonstrated ability to work in an environment where procedures and controls are required<br>Strong computer skills, with ability to learn and easily adapt to new application.<br>High level of accuracy, and ability to analyze complex trade data and identify discrepancies.<br>Proactively identify issues and develop solutions.<br>Client focused with the ability to understand the requirements of clients<br>Must have the ability to create and maintain strong relationships with people at all levels and different functions throughout the organization and with external partners<br>Quick learner and solutions oriented, ability to escalate issues to management<br>Ability to react quickly and meet tight deadlines maintaining accuracy and thoroughness<br>Excellent English skills, both oral and written, with strong comprehension skills to effectively communicate with internal and external stakeholders<br>Demonstrate initiative and team player<br>Ability to adapt to changes, and set priorities<br> When you join our team:<br> We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br> We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br> As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Manulife: Lead Full Stack Software Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Makati-City/Lead-Full-Stack-Software-Engineer_JR25091502?_ga=2.221645648.910128295.1720975398-2145552937.1720975398&geotagText=CA/L4S%202V1/Richmond%20Hill&distance=a538cdb60a631000078a2c71efcc00f6]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Makati City<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: December 31, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR25091502<br>The position is responsible for the Software Engineering leadership, application architecture, development and support of new and existing strategic digital application platforms for Manulife Asia.<br>Position Responsibilities: <br>Application Architecture, Development and Support<br>Technical leadership in Software Engineering for Manulife’s Digital Strategic Applications.<br>Assist in the gathering and analysis of user requirements and provide consultation on estimates, sprint planning and validating / qualifying estimates provided by development teams and third parties.<br>Translate user requirements into software requirements<br>Assess application architecture impact and follow sound systems design principles, maximizing reuse of components and flexibility in configuration of design to support multiple country, sales channel, and life insurance product requirements.<br>Maintain the quality standards of the application platform, ensuring robust QA and code review processes are in place.<br>Establish and adhere to DevSecOps practices to maximize automation and continuous delivery practices, including comprehensive unit test automation.<br>Maintain systems development standards, patterns and ensure compliance.<br>Prepare and maintain full technical documentation of development tasks and deliverables<br>Troubleshoot system errors reported by users<br>Apply change management principles where appropriate in the IT process to effectively deliver solutions<br>Ensure IT operational SLA compliance and operational efficiency of IT processes in support of business goals<br>Define and promote software engineering standards<br>Collaborate with fellow Lead Software Engineers in the region to build an exciting and innovative culture within the teams across Manulife Asia<br>Contribute to the reuse of digital technology, solutions & skills to achieve cost efficiencies utilizing Agile, DevSecOps, repeatable technical playbooks and collaborative IT process automation practices.<br>Open for travel within Asia Region.<br>People Development/Leadership <br>Provide technical leadership to one or more agile delivery squads.<br>Participate/lead in cross training and up skilling activities for other software engineers<br>Help onboard, train, and mentor new members in the team<br>Coach software engineers in the Asia region for Manulife’s Technology Transformation<br>                                                                                                                                                         Software Engineering Leadership<br>Ensure programming best practices & quality gates are followed<br>Ability to drive new technology analysis & discussion<br>Ability to deliver under high pressure<br>Ensure application integrity as product roadmap & business requirements.<br>Committed team player<br>Proven track record of developing applications using Agile methodology.<br>Required Qualifications:<br>General<br>Passionate about software engineering.<br>Built applications for large number of users and dealing with the challenges this brings.<br>Good understanding of design patterns, and why and when to use them.<br>Works in a structured logical way and does not just jump into new technology without fully understanding it.<br>Previous experience setting up patterns for other engineers to follow and provide mentoring to the wider team.<br>Previous experience designing application architectures<br>Education<br>Bachelor degree or equivalent in Computing Science or Engineering<br>Experience<br>A minimum of 15 years of experience in designing and developing integrated digital solutions.<br>Extensive experience in building Microservices and Cloud Native Applications<br>Extensive experience in delivering user-centric front-end applications (web and/or mobile)<br>Experience in delivering projects from inception through to post-implementation warranty using Agile DevSecOps project delivery methodologies.<br>Expert level experience of cloud PaaS services (Azure, AWS, Google Cloud Platform)<br>Experience in delivering projects involving stakeholders from multiple locations<br>Solid understanding of software delivery processes and tools (i.e. distributed version control systems, CI/CD)<br>Recognize the importance of high quality code through non-negotiables like unit tests, integration/acceptance tests, performant, secure.<br>Solid experience in implementing Site Reliability Engineering Principles and Practices for Enterprise Level Software Applications<br>Solid experience in Cloud Security Concepts<br>Insurance industry knowledge is seen as advantageous<br>Technical Skills<br>Expert knowledge of Cloud Services, preferably Azure.<br>Expert knowledge in OOP frameworks and libraries, preferably Java Springboot and/or NodeJS.<br>Expert knowledge in Cloud Native Development using PaaS solutions and containerization<br>Expert knowledge in API Driven Development<br>Expert knowledge in modern front-end web technologies, including Single Page Applications, Web Components, Service Workers and micro-frontends.<br>Expert knowledge in API Gateways, Messaging, Data Event Streaming, REST, Distributed Tracing, Relational and Document Database Interface/SQL<br>Expert knowledge in using telemetry and observability tools, such as New Relic, ELK Stack<br>Experience in the design, development and testing of microservices<br>Delivery methodology Agile, TDD/BDD/DDD within DevSecOps environment<br>Knowledge of Mobile Application Development<br>Knowledge of Salesforce and/or Microsoft Dynamics<br>When you join our team:<br>We’ll empower you to learn and grow the career you want.<br>We’ll recognize and support you in a flexible environment where well-being and inclusion are more than just words.<br>As part of our global team, we’ll support you in shaping the future you want to see.<br>About Manulife and John Hancock<br>Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider, helping people make their decisions easier and lives better. To learn more about us, visit https://www.manulife.com/en/about/our-story.html.<br>Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer<br>At Manulife/John Hancock, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract, develop and retain a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, retention, advancement and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin, colour, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.<br>It is our priority to remove barriers to provide equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process. All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies. To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact recruitment@manulife.com.<br>Working Arrangement<br>Hybrid]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>