<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: AI SoC CAD Development Lead Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/AI-SoC-CAD-Software-Development-Lead-Engineer_JR0277470?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277470<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>We are seeking a highly experienced Lead Engineer to conceptualize, document, and design Tools, Flows, and Methods (TFM) that enhance logic/RTL design for IPs and SoCs. This role focuses on improving design efficiency, quality, and integration across architectures and process nodes. You will work closely with logic design teams to define and implement methodologies that drive improvements in power, performance, and area (PPA), while enabling fast convergence and seamless integration.<br>Key Responsibilities<br>Design and develop TFM solutions for logic/RTL design and IP/SoC integration.<br>Define and implement methodologies that optimize PPA on advanced architectures and process nodes.<br>Analyze retrospective data to identify gaps and propose incremental or transformative improvements.<br>Collaborate with logic design teams to enhance RTL design flows and convergence strategies.<br>Develop automation and infrastructure to support RTL development, simulation, and physical design.<br>Qualifications:<br>Required Qualifications<br>BS/MS in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field with 10+ years of experience.<br>8+ years of experience in semiconductor design in areas such as RTL simulation, design verification and/or synthesis.<br>Proficiency in Python for software development.<br>Familiarity with EDA data formats such as Liberty, SDC, SDF, VCD/FSDB.<br>Experience working with Git in large collaborative development environments.<br>Familiarity with industry-standard EDA tools and front-end design flows (RTL, simulation, verification, linting, synthesis).<br>Excellent debugging and problem-solving skills with a focus on software robustness and maintainability.<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Advanced proficiency in Python, with strong object-oriented design skills.<br>Knowledge of build systems (e.g., Make, CMake, Gradle) and dependency management.<br>Experience with cloud-based or hybrid on-prem/cloud development environments.<br>Proficiency in Docker and Kubernetes for containerized EDA workflows.<br>Ability to thrive in a fast-paced, collaborative environment.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>As a member of the Chief Technology Office, Artificial Intelligence, and Network and Edge Group (CTO AI NEX), you will be committed to strategically penetrating the AI market by delivering disruptive and transformative solutions. Your focus will be on leveraging technology innovation and incubation to drive commercial success, ensuring that advancements create significant value. The team is dedicated to driving the software-defined transformation of the world's networks profitably, setting new standards for efficiency and connectivity. Through these priorities, you aim to lead the way in technological evolution and redefine the future of global networks.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>This role is a Position of Trust. Should you accept this position, you must consent to and pass an extended Background Investigation, which includes (subject to country law), extended education, SEC sanctions, and additional criminal and civil checks. For internals, this investigation may or may not be completed prior to starting the position. For additional questions, please contact your Recruiter.<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$204,500.00-$288,710.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Sr. Infrastructure Engineer – Windows OS]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Sr-Infrastructure-Engineer---Windows-OS_JR0277459?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277459<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Foundry Automation group is seeking an experienced Infrastructure Windows Engineer - Government Programs.<br>In this role, you will be responsible for deploying, configuring, and managing Windows Server OS. This role also involves managing various layered applications such as enterprise software, middleware, and security tools, ensuring that they perform efficiently, securely in alignment with key initiatives driving towards Intel Foundry's success. You will bring expertise in automation to streamline processes and enhance the overall efficiency of our Windows Server Infrastructure.<br>The ideal candidate is a dynamic leader with experience managing complex projects to achieve organizational goals. Success in this role requires adaptability and flexibility in a fast-paced environment.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>• Manage the full lifecycle of Windows Server OS environments, including installation, configuration, patching, performance tuning, and security hardening.<br>• Deploy, configure, and maintain layered applications, including middleware (e.g., .NET, IIS), enterprise software (e.g., Active Directory, Microsoft Exchange, SQL Server), and security applications (e.g., antivirus, firewalls).<br>• Oversee integration and compatibility of layered applications, ensuring they operate seamlessly on Windows Server OS and within network and security standards.<br>• Implement automation scripts (PowerShell, Python) to streamline repetitive tasks, maintain layered applications, and improve system reliability.<br>• Apply security best practices for both OS and layered applications, including patch management, vulnerability scanning, and access control.<br>• Conduct performance monitoring and tuning of both OS and layered applications to ensure system responsiveness and minimize downtime.<br>• Troubleshoot complex OS and application-level issues, working cross-functionally to ensure minimal disruption to business operations.<br>• Develop and maintain documentation for configurations, integrations, and troubleshooting steps related to layered applications and the OS environment.<br>• Collaborate with network and security teams to ensure compliance with company policies, data integrity, and optimal performance across the infrastructure.<br>The ideal candidate should demonstrate:<br>• Deep expertise with Windows Server environments, including specific experience with Win2k19 and Win2k22.<br>• Strong knowledge of layered applications, middleware, and integration within Windows-based environments.<br>• Advanced skills in automation scripting (e.g., PowerShell, VBS) to streamline Windows OS management.<br>• Strong understanding of security principles and the ability to apply these to Windows OS and application layers.<br>• Excellent troubleshooting and problem-solving skills, with the ability to resolve complex issues in Windows OS and layered applications.<br>• Some travel required.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications<br>• U.S. citizenship required.<br>• Ability to obtain and maintain US Government TS Security Clearance and SCI access.<br>• Bachelor's degree or higher in Computer Science or a related STEM field.<br>• 3+ years of experience in Windows Server infrastructure engineering and layered apps (such as Active Directory (AD), DHCP, DNS, MSFC, NLB, Antivirus and Malware Protection/Scanning, MFA, IIS, Patching, Debug Tools, Monitoring, Manageability, PKI, etc).<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>• 5+ years' experience in Windows Server OS environments, including configuration, tuning, and support for various layered applications.<br>• Experience with automation and scripting, particularly with PowerShell (VBS or other scripting languages a plus), to streamline OS and application management.<br>• Experience with security standards and compliance frameworks (e.g., NIST, CIS) and implementing security best practices for layered applications and OS.<br>• Experience in troubleshooting skills and experience in diagnosing issues across OS, middleware, enterprise applications, and security tools.<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Sr. Infrastructure Engineer – Linux OS]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Sr-Infrastructure-Engineer---Linux-OS_JR0277458?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277458<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Foundry Automation group is seeking an experienced Infrastructure Linux Engineer - Government Programs In this role, you will be responsible for deploying, configuring, and managing Linux OS environments, particularly with a focus on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL).<br>The role also involves managing various layered applications such as enterprise software, middleware, and security tools, ensuring they perform efficiently and securely in alignment with key initiatives driving towards Intel Foundry's success. You will bring expertise in automation to streamline processes and enhance the overall efficiency of our Linux infrastructure.<br>The ideal candidate is a proactive engineer with experience managing complex projects to achieve organizational goals. Success in this role requires adaptability and flexibility in a fast-paced environment.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>• Manage the full lifecycle of Linux OS environments, specifically RHEL, covering installation, configuration, patching, performance tuning, and security hardening. • Deploy, configure, and maintain layered applications, including middleware (e.g., Apache, Tomcat), enterprise software (e.g., LDAP, MySQL, PostgreSQL), and security applications (e.g., SELinux configurations, firewalls).<br>• Oversee integration and compatibility of layered applications, ensuring seamless operation within the RHEL environment and alignment with network and security standards.<br>• Implement automation scripts (e.g., Bash, Python) to streamline repetitive tasks, maintain layered applications, and improve system reliability.<br>• Apply security best practices to the Linux OS and layered applications, including patch management, vulnerability scanning, and access control.<br>• Conduct performance monitoring and tuning of both OS and layered applications to ensure system responsiveness and uptime.<br>• Troubleshoot complex OS and application-level issues, collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure minimal disruption to operations.<br>• Develop and maintain documentation for configurations, integrations, and troubleshooting steps related to layered applications and the Linux OS environment. • Collaborate with network and security teams to ensure compliance with company policies, data integrity, and optimal performance across the infrastructure.<br>The ideal candidate should demonstrate:<br>• Deep expertise with Linux OS environments, specifically RHEL7 and RHEL8, and extensive experience in Linux lifecycle management.<br>• Strong knowledge of layered applications, middleware, and integration within Linux-based environments.<br>• Advanced skills in automation scripting (e.g., Bash, Python) to streamline Linux OS and application management.<br>• Strong understanding of security principles and the ability to apply these to Linux OS and application layers.<br>• Excellent troubleshooting and problem-solving skills, with the ability to resolve complex issues in Linux OS and layered applications.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications<br>• U.S. citizenship required.<br>• Ability to obtain and maintain US Government TS Security Clearance and SCI access.<br>• Bachelor's or Master's Degree in Computer Science or a related STEM field.<br>• 2+ years of experience in Linux infrastructure engineering, with an emphasis on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) environments.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>• Experience in Linux OS environments, particularly RHEL, including configuration, tuning, and support for various layered applications.<br>• Experience in automation and scripting, particularly in Bash or Python (other scripting languages a plus), to streamline OS and application management.<br>• Experience with security standards and compliance frameworks (e.g., NIST, CIS) and implementing security best practices for layered applications and Linux OS.<br>• Experience in troubleshooting skills and experience in diagnosing issues across OS, middleware, enterprise applications, and security tools.<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>#CJ<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Sr. Infrastructure Engineer – Virtualization and Cloud Platforms]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Sr-Infrastructure-Engineer---Virtualization-and-Cloud-Platforms_JR0277457?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277457<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Foundry Automation group is seeking an experienced Infrastructure Virtualization and Cloud Platforms Engineer - Government Programs. In this role, you will be responsible for engineering, deploying, and managing our on-prem cloud stack and leverage CI/CD tools to enhance and automate infrastructure processes. You will oversee the design and management of virtualization environments (primarily VMware) ensuring high performance and availability. Security will be at the forefront of your approach, as you work to ensure that infrastructure solutions adhere to best practices and compliance standards in alignment with key initiatives driving towards Intel Foundry's success.<br>The ideal candidate is a proactive engineer with experience managing complex projects to achieve organizational goals. Success in this role requires adaptability and flexibility in a fast-paced environment.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>• Engineer, deploy, and support on-prem cloud infrastructure, ensuring it meets organizational needs for resilience, scalability, and operational efficiency.<br>• Oversee the design, configuration, and optimization of virtualization platforms, including VMware, focusing on stability, performance, and cost-effectiveness.<br>• Develop and implement CI/CD pipelines to streamline provisioning, automate deployment processes, and support infrastructure-as-code practices.<br>• Collaborate with cross-functional teams to integrate CI/CD tools and practices that enhance deployment speed and reliability within the on-prem cloud and virtualization environments.<br>• Integrate and manage layered security practices across all infrastructure, from access control to network security, aligned with NIST guidelines.<br>• Monitor and fine-tune infrastructure performance, resource allocation, and capacity planning within on-prem cloud and VMware environments.<br>• Troubleshoot complex infrastructure issues, providing advanced support for cloud and virtualization technologies to minimize downtime.<br>• Create and maintain comprehensive documentation for infrastructure configurations, operational procedures, and troubleshooting guides.<br>• Stay current with emerging trends in cloud, virtualization, automation, and security to drive continuous infrastructure improvement.<br>The ideal candidate should demonstrate:<br>• Strong expertise in on-prem cloud infrastructure and VMware virtualization, with a comprehensive understanding of deployment, maintenance, and scaling. • Proficiency in CI/CD practices and infrastructure-as-code tools to streamline management and improve reliability.<br>• In-depth knowledge of NIST standards and experience applying them within on-prem and virtualized infrastructures.<br>• Excellent problem-solving skills with a proven ability to troubleshoot complex issues in cloud, virtualized, and CI/CD environments.<br>• Effective communication and collaboration skills, working across teams to implement best practices and drive continuous improvement.<br>•Effective communication and collaboration skills, working across teams to implement best practices and drive continuous improvement.<br>• Some travel required.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>• U.S. citizenship required.<br>• Ability to obtain and maintain US Government TS Security Clearance and SCI access.<br>• Bachelor's degree or higher in Computer Science or a related STEM field.<br>•4+ years of experience with on-prem cloud (such as Rancher or Openshift) and virtualization technologies (such as VMware or KubeVirt).<br><br>Preferred Qualifications: <br>•Active US Government TS/SCI<br>• Experience with virtualization platforms, particularly VMware, including setup, management, and troubleshooting.<br>• Experience with cloud-native tools, containerization (e.g., Docker, Kubernetes), and their integration within on-prem cloud and virtualized environments.<br>• Experience in CI/CD tools (e.g., GitHub, Ansible) and infrastructure-as-code methodologies• Scripting experience in Python, Bash, PowerShell or similar languages to support automation and improve operational workflows.<br>• Experience with monitoring and logging solutions (e.g., Prometheus, ELK Stack) for proactive infrastructure management aligned with NIST standards.<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Sr. Infrastructure Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Sr-Infrastructure-Engineer_JR0277456?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277456<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Foundry Automation group is seeking an experienced Infrastructure Engineer - Government Programs. In this role, you will focus on server hardware management, lifecycle management, and operating systems (Linux and Windows). You will be responsible for the deployment, configuration, and troubleshooting of data center servers, ensuring system stability, performance, and security in alignment with key initiatives driving Intel Foundry's success. Your expertise in server hardware will be essential for optimizing our hardware infrastructure and supporting operational efficiency.<br>The ideal candidate is a dynamic leader with experience managing complex projects to achieve organizational goals. Success requires adaptability and flexibility in a fast-paced environment.<br>Responsibilities Include:<br>• Overseeing the full server lifecycle, from landing and provisioning to maintenance, in a data center environment.<br>• Troubleshooting and resolving hardware and software issues on servers, storage, and operating systems (Linux, Windows).<br>• Using tools such as iLO (Integrated Lights-Out) and BMC (Baseboard Management Controller).<br>• Ensure the installation and maintenance of firmware and drivers for server hardware to optimize performance and compatibility across systems.<br>• Managing server builds, including provisioning via PXE boot and other automated deployment technologies.<br>• Configuring and maintaining hardware components, including various storage drives (HDD, SSD, NVMe) and ensuring optimal network and storage connectivity.<br>• Collaborating with network, storage, and security teams to support infrastructure needs and resolve cross-functional technical issues.<br>• Conducting OS patching, upgrades, and configuration changes to maintain system security and efficiency.<br>• Monitoring and optimizing server performance, capacity planning, and hardware utilization.<br>• Supporting backup, data integrity, and disaster recovery processes in line with best practices.<br>• Documenting procedures, configurations, and changes for server and hardware management.<br>• Staying current with emerging server technologies and practices for continuous improvement of data center operations.<br>• Some travel may be required.<br>The ideal candidate should demonstrate:<br>• Expertise in server hardware (HPE, Dell), including different drive types (HDD, SSD, NVMe), network and storage connectivity, and server troubleshooting with tools like iLO and BMC.<br>• Expertise in OS troubleshooting (Linux, Windows).<br>• Strong analytical and troubleshooting skills for diagnosing complex infrastructure issues.<br>• Deep understanding of automated deployment technologies, such as PXE boot, for consistent server builds.<br>• Proficiency in automation using scripting languages (e.g., Bash, Python, PowerShell) for server management.<br>• A proactive approach to identifying and resolving issues across multi-functional infrastructure teams.<br>• Excellent documentation skills with a focus on precision and consistency in managing complex systems.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>• U.S. citizenship required.<br>• Ability to obtain and maintain US Government TS Security Clearance and SCI access.<br>• Bachelor's degree or higher in Computer Science or a related STEM field.<br>• 4+ years of experience in infrastructure engineering, with a strong emphasis on server hardware and its lifecycle management.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>• Experience in server hardware, storage infrastructure, and OS troubleshooting (Linux, Windows).<br>• Experience with scripting languages (e.g., Bash, Python, PowerShell) for automation of server management tasks.<br>• Experience in networking fundamentals with respect to software-defined networks like ACI.<br>• Experience with best practices for data center security, power, and cooling to support reliable infrastructure design.<br>• Experience with security compliance standards and best practices for data center management, including the server hardware and operating system lifecycle.<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>#CJ<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Sr. Infrastructure Engineer – Storage]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Sr-Infrastructure-Engineer---Storage_JR0277455?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277455<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Foundry Automation group is seeking an experienced Infrastructure Storage Engineer - Government Programs. In this role, you will lead the development, optimization, and integration of advanced storage technologies-object, file, and block storage, as well as software-defined storage-across service models like bare metal, IaaS, and PaaS.<br>This role is central to designing, implementing, maintaining, and scaling our high-performance, on-premise storage solutions in alignment with key initiatives driving towards Intel Foundry's success. You will also resolve storage issues and collaborate with software engineering teams to create scalable, supportable platforms. A strong understanding of storage architecture, operations, and scalability is essential to ensure reliability, performance, and support for future growth.<br>The ideal candidate is a dynamic leader with experience managing complex projects to achieve organizational goals. Success requires adaptability and flexibility in a fast-paced environment.<br>Responsibilities include:<br>• Plan, manage, and optimize installation, configuration, and tuning of SAN, Software Defined Storage (SDS), NAS, S3, and backup solutions such as Veeam, SnapVault, etc.<br>• Design and implement scalable storage and backup infrastructure modifications; assist and document configuration changes across the environment.<br>• Stay current with storage and backup technologies, including solutions like Rubrik, Cohesity, and DataDomain, along with product enhancements and roadmaps to ensure reliable, state-of-the-art storage and data protection.<br>• Develop and enforce policies for consistent provisioning, uptime, data protection, and backup integrity; ensure regulatory compliance and data security.<br>• Track storage and backup usage, project future growth, manage data migrations, and enhance configurations to optimize system performance.<br>• Monitor performance, utilization, and troubleshoot issues to maintain data integrity; oversee daily storage and backup operations and hardware maintenance.<br>• Lead storage and backup infrastructure projects, apply best practices, support disaster recovery strategies, and document standard procedures.<br>The ideal candidate should demonstrate:<br>• In-depth knowledge of SAN, NAS, SDS, and Object Storage technologies, including configuration, performance tuning, and troubleshooting; proficient in storage protocols such as Fibre Channel (FC), NFS, SMB, and S3.<br>• Hands-on experience with enterprise backup solutions (e.g., Veeam, SnapVault) for data protection and disaster recovery, including backup configuration, scheduling, and data restoration.<br>• Strong background in on-premises storage infrastructure, including physical and virtualized environments, with familiarity in hybrid cloud integration.<br>• Solid understanding of general system administration and solutions architecture principles, including server configuration, storage provisioning, and network integration to ensure robust storage operations.<br>• Experience with automation tools like Ansible and Python, and expertise in software-defined solutions such as Microsoft Storage Spaces Direct (S2D) to enhance efficiency and scalability in storage management.<br>• Strong troubleshooting and analytical skills to proactively resolve storage issues, analyze usage patterns, and design scalable storage solutions to meet current and future business needs.<br>• Effective in collaborating with both technical and non-technical teams, aligning storage strategies with business goals and clearly communicating complex technical information.<br>• Some travel required.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications: <br>• U.S. citizenship required.<br>• Ability to obtain and maintain US Government TS Security Clearance and SCI access.<br>• Bachelor's degree or higher in Computer Science or a related STEM field.<br>• 3+ years of experience in storage configuration for physical and virtualized environments.<br><br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>• 5+ years of experience in storage configuration for physical and virtualized environments.<br>•Active US Government TS/SCI.<br>• Experience in scripting languages like Python, PowerShell, or Bash for automation of storage tasks.<br>• Experience in data protection, disaster recovery, high-availability solutions, and familiarity with backup tools.<br>• Experience with virtualization platforms and container storage solutions.<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Engineering Analytics Developer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Folsom/Engineering-Analytics-Developer_JR0277350?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Folsom<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, Texas, Austin<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277350<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Job Summary<br>Create and maintain dashboards, KPIs, and data pipelines to track engineering performance for Silicon development (Semiconductor). Work with engineering, program management, and BI teams to turn complex data into clear insights that drive better decision-making.<br>Key Responsibilities<br>Build and maintain Power BI dashboards and engineering performance indicators<br>Develop data pipelines and ensure data quality across engineering datasets<br>Partner with engineering teams and program management to define KPIs<br>Transform complex data into actionable insights for stakeholders<br>Support data governance and best practices across the organization<br>The ideal candidate must exhibit: <br>Strong communication skills and ability to work with cross-functional teams<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum Qualifications<br>Bachelor's or Master's in Data Science, Computer Science, Engineering, or related field<br>7+ years experience in BI development, analytics, or data science<br>The years of experience must include:<br>Skills in Power BI, SQL, and Python<br>Designing KPI frameworks and data modeling<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Semiconductor or technology industry background<br>Experience with Databricks and cloud analytics platforms<br>Executive communication and stakeholder management experience<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Folsom<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix, US, Oregon, Hillsboro, US, Texas, Austin<br>Business group:<br>The Platform Engineering Group (PEG) defines, architects, validates and deploys all Intel’s platforms. PEG works across Intel’s product portfolio and engineering functions to ensure our platforms maximize value to our customers, their users and Intel’s business.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$129,890.00-$183,370.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will be eligible for our hybrid work model which allows employees to split their time between working on-site at their assigned Intel site and off-site. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Network Security Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Network-Security-Analyst_JR0277300?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277300<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>The world is transforming - and so is Intel. Intel is a company of bold and curious inventors and problem solvers who create some of the most astounding technology advancements and experiences in the world. With a legacy of relentless innovation and a commitment to bring smart, connected devices to every person on Earth, our diverse and brilliant teams are continually searching for tomorrow's technology and revel in the challenge that changing the world for the better brings. We work every single day to design and manufacture silicon products that empower people's digital lives. Come join us and do something wonderful.<br>Who we Are:<br>Intel's Information Security organization enables Intel to provide secure products, solutions, and services which meet U.S. regulatory requirements. The Information Security organization supports the unique IT information Security and Compliance requirements for Intel federal projects that deliver products and/or services to the US Government (USG). As part of this team, you will help us grow our secure solution suite to meet U.S. Government requirements. The Intel Information Security organization is seeking a Network Security Engineer. The candidate chosen for this role will assist senior engineers with design, architecture, and build of secure classified network products to support USG operations.<br>Primary duties and responsibilities:<br>Assist with architecting network and network security products in secured enclaves, including product testing, validation, and selection.<br>Assist with design and long-term roadmap planning for new and future scalability in secure enclaves.<br>Play a supporting role with the definition of system security requirements, including but not limited to the authorization boundary, security domains, classification of data, etc.<br>Assist with design of the security interfaces, security interconnections, and the trust relationship between system components and external systems. Implement system security designs using commercial-off-the-shelf (COTS), government-off- the-shelf (GOTS), and open-source hardware and software. Oversee the hardening and configuration systems and system components in accordance with various Federal, Department of Defense (DoD), and Intelligence Community (IC) guidance.<br>Coordinate security assessments to identify security control failures and recommend corrective actions.<br>Business travel is required as needed.<br>#cj<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. Experience listed below would be obtained through a combination of your degree, research and or relevant previous job and or internship experiences.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>US Citizenship required.<br>The ability to obtain and maintain a US Government Top Secret Security Clearance<br>High School /Equivalent Diploma and 3+ years of applicable experience with at least one of the following certifications: CCNA, CCNP, Network+, etc. CISSP, CISM, CASP E, Security+ OR Bachelor's degree and 2+ years of applicable experience.<br>2+ years of experience in the following:<br>Event monitoring and alerting system management.<br>Scripting for automation and configuration management, secure coding and encryption techniques in an enterprise environment<br>Event monitoring and modeling using enterprise caliber tools/applications• Microsoft and Linux environments in an enterprise information security environment.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Active US Government Top Secret (TS) Security Clearance with the ability to obtain and maintain SCI access<br>Bachelor's degree in Systems Engineering, Cyber Security Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, Information Systems, or similar discipline and four years of work-related experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience<br>Experience with DoD security implementation (e.g. STIG) and security tools for managing the environment<br>Experience with business continuity and disaster recovery.<br>Experience with network analysis software such as SD Elements, Splunk, Sniffer, Wireshark, or Microsoft Network Monitor<br>Experience automating processes supporting configuration management and process improvement<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Business group:<br>Join Intel's Finance Group, a key player in driving strategic business decisions that enhance shareholder value. Our team is dedicated to facilitating change and improvement across finance and the operations we support. As strategic partners, we lead acquisitions and inorganic growth initiatives, managing transactions from ideation to completion while serving as trusted advisors to executive leadership. We also design and support Intel’s IT infrastructure, driving e-Commerce and web services with a focus on robust security and identity protection. Our innovative supply chain solutions propel Intel’s market initiatives, ensuring seamless support and maximizing revenue opportunities. Additionally, we enhance employee experiences by maintaining Intel sites globally and advancing environmental sustainability efforts.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$117,270.00-$165,550.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: MCP Emulation Verification Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Oregon-Hillsboro/MCP-Emulation-Verification-Engineer_JR0277364?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook<br>US, California, Folsom<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Texas, Austin<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277364<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Do Something Wonderful!<br>Intel put Silicon in Silicon Valley. No one else is obsessed with engineering and has a brighter future. Every day, we create world changing technology that enriches the lives of every person on earth. So, if you have a big idea, let's do something wonderful together. Join us, because at Intel, we are building a better tomorrow.<br>Who We Are<br>Our team mainly works on Xeon servers. The work involves SOC level pre-si validation using emulation and also act as a bridge between the IP/ die validation and post-silicon teams. Our team focuses on validation of end-to-end validation.<br>Who You Are<br>Your responsibilities will include but are not limited to:<br>Performs functional logic verification of an integrated SoC to ensure design will meet specifications.<br>Defines and develops scalable and reusable block, subsystem, and SoC verification plans, test benches, and the verification environment to meet the required level of coverage and confirm microarchitecture specifications.<br>Executes verification plans and defines and runs emulation and system simulation models to verify the design, analyze power and performance, and uncover bugs. Replicates, root causes, and debugs issues in the presilicon environment.<br>Finds and implements corrective measures to resolve failing tests. Collaborates and communicates with SoC architects, micro-architects, full chip architects, RTL developers, postsilicon, and physical design teams to improve verification of complex architectural and microarchitectural features.<br>Documents test plans and drive technical reviews of plans and proofs with design and architecture teams. Incorporates and executes security activities within test plans, including regression and debug tests, to ensure security coverage.<br>Maintains and improves existing functional verification infrastructure and methodology.<br>Absorbs learning from postsilicon on the quality of validation done during presilicon development, updates test plan for missing coverages and proliferates to future products.<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the minimum education requirements and minimum required qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Additional preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br> Minimum Qualifications<br>The candidate must have a Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Engineering/Computer Science/Electrical Engineering or STEM related field with 3+ years of relevant experience -OR- Master’s Degree in Computer Engineering/Computer Science/Electrical Engineering or STEM related field with 2+ years of relevant experience<br>2+ years of work experience in Pre-Silicon Validation on Emulation<br>2+ years of work experience in complex SOC validation with multiple IPs<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Experience with Synopsys simulation and coverage tools.<br>Assertion based verification<br>Knowledge in RTL, Verilog, VHDL<br>Experience in validation at MCP<br>Experience with pre-Si verification with System Verilog OVM/UVM on content development Scripting languages such as Python, Simics.<br>Knowledge of CPU architecture and X86<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, California, Folsom, US, California, Santa Clara, US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook, US, Texas, Austin<br>Business group:<br>The Silicon Engineering Group (SIG) is a worldwide organization focused on the development and integration of SOCs, Cores, and critical IPs from architecture to manufacturing readiness that power Intel’s leadership products. This business group leverages an incomparable mix of experts with different backgrounds, cultures, perspectives, and experiences to unleash the most innovative, amazing, and exciting computing experiences.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$133,050.00-$187,840.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Senior IP Design Verification Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Senior-IP-Design-Verification-Engineer_JR0277347?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277347<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Do Something Wonderful!<br>Intel put Silicon in Silicon Valley. No one else is obsessed with engineering and has a brighter future. Every day, we create world changing technology that enriches the lives of every person on earth. So, if you have a big idea, let's do something wonderful together. Join us, because at Intel, we are building a better tomorrow.<br>Who We Are<br>Become a key member of a team participating in the Integration and Verification of a future Intel CPU. This position requires and Engineer with broad Physical Design and Static Timing Analysis skills, coupled with leadership skills necessary to drive methodology and to collaborate effectively with multiple functional teams within the CPU design team.<br>Who You Are<br>Responsibilities may include but are not limited to:<br>Performs functional verification of IP logic to ensure design will meet specification requirements.<br>Develops IP verification plans, test benches, and the verification environment to ensure coverage to confirm microarchitecture specifications.<br>Executes verification plans and defines and runs system simulation models to verify the design, analyze power and timing, and uncover bugs.<br>Replicates, root causes, and debugs issues in the presilicon environment.<br>Finds and implements corrective measures to resolve failing tests.<br>Collaborates with architects, RTL developers, and physical design teams to improve verification of complex architectural and microarchitectural features.<br>Documents test plans and drive technical reviews of plans and proofs with design and architecture teams.<br>Maintains and improves existing functional verification infrastructure and methodology.<br>Participates in the definition of verification infrastructure and related TFMs needed for functional design verification.<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the minimum education requirements and minimum required qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Additional preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br> Minimum Qualifications<br>The candidate must have a Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Engineering/Computer Science or Electrical Engineering with 4+ years of relevant experience -OR- a Master’s Degree in Computer Engineering Computer Science or Electrical Engineering with 3+ years of relevant experience with C and Object-Oriented Software design including algorithms and data structures -OR- PhD in Computer Engineering/Computer Science or Electrical Engineering<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Proficiency in System C System Verilog UVM and ESL modeling methodologies<br>Proficiency in HW design and verification methodologies<br>Working knowledge of highspeed HW protocols eg PCIe UPI DDR<br>Knowledge of Software development practices and quality standards<br>Experience with Unix Windows based SW development tools.<br>Experience developing bus functional models for unit level verification or Verification IP development<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook, US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Business group:<br>The Silicon Engineering Group (SIG) is a worldwide organization focused on the development and integration of SOCs, Cores, and critical IPs from architecture to manufacturing readiness that power Intel’s leadership products. This business group leverages an incomparable mix of experts with different backgrounds, cultures, perspectives, and experiences to unleash the most innovative, amazing, and exciting computing experiences.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$153,540.00-$216,770.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: GPU Software Development Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Folsom/GPU-Software-Development-Engineer_JR0277307?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Folsom<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277307<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Role Overview:<br>Develop and validate software for Intel GPUs, covering the entire stack from firmware and device drivers to APIs and application layers. This may also include tools, infrastructure, and technologies for developing, profiling, optimizing, and productizing Intel GPUs or graphics/GPGPU software solutions.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>Drive Graphics Software feature health post-silicon, focusing on functionality, power, and performance from an end-to-end perspective.<br>Understand feature architecture and manage end-to-end graphics usage, emphasizing concurrency, reliability, stress, and interoperability, particularly in content creation and AI.<br>Scale across display, media, 3D, compute, and power conservation, with a focus on user experience. Requires deep knowledge of OS architecture, GEN graphics architecture, graphics driver software architecture, and power/performance goals.<br>Develop and enable advanced machine learning/deep learning and media workloads on next-generation graphics platforms.<br>Triage and debug end-to-end test failures, collaborating with software and hardware teams to resolve issues.<br>Provide feedback to implement upcoming graphics features in unreleased operating systems, ensuring hardware and software functionality and performance on future platforms.<br>Design, develop, and implement graphics system-level software for future platforms.<br>Ideal Candidate Traits:<br>Strong quantitative, analytical, and problem-solving skills.<br>Qualifications:<br> To be initially considered for this position, you must meet the minimum qualifications listed below. Preferred qualifications are additional and can help identify top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>Education:<br>Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering, or a related STEM field with 4+ years of relevant experience.<br>OR Master's degree in the same fields with 2+ years of relevant experience.<br>Experience must be in:<br>Windows OS and X86 CPU architectures.<br>Understanding of Intel GPU hardware architecture.<br>GPU software development, validation, and Kernel-level experience<br>Knowledge in Graphic drivers focusing on functionality, power, and performance<br>Programming languages C and C++.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Folsom<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>The Client Computing Group (CCG) is responsible for driving business strategy and product development for Intel's PC products and platforms, spanning form factors such as notebooks, desktops, 2 in 1s, all in ones. Working with our partners across the industry, we intend to deliver purposeful computing experiences that unlock people's potential - allowing each person use our products to focus, create and connect in ways that matter most to them.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$139,540.00-$197,000.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Software Application Development Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Software-Application-Development-Engineer_JR0277472?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277472<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel is shaping the future of technology to help create a better future for the entire world. Our work in pushing forward fields like AI, analytics, and cloud-to-edge technology is at the heart of countless innovations. With a career at Intel, you'll have the opportunity to use technology to power major breakthroughs and create enhancements that improve our everyday quality of life. Join us and help make the future more wonderful for everyone. Want to learn more? Visit our YouTube Channel or the links below. <br> Life at Intel<br>Diversity at Intel<br>As an Intel Mask Operations (IMO) Software Application Development Engineer, you will join an energetic, diverse group of engineers developing complex manufacturing automation solutions. You collaborate with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality, scalable, and efficient software solutions.<br>This will enable Intel to be one generation ahead in technology. <br>As a Software Application Development Engineer, you will <br>Designs, develops, tests, and debugs software applications used by end users or integrated with other applications.<br>Development may span the entire application stack, including frontend and backend application development.<br>Uses modern software development methodologies and programming languages, follows secure coding practices and software legal compliance guidelines, analyzes user stories, writes functional and test code, automates build and deployment, and performs unit integration and end-to-end testing of applications. Completes product documentation and procedures for installation and maintenance.<br>May also interact with end users to define system requirements and/or necessary modifications.<br>Qualifications:<br>Qualifications<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br><br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>US Citizenship required.<br>Ability to obtain a US Government Security Clearance.<br>Bachelor's degree in computer science or a related field and 1+ years' relevant work experience.<br>6+ months experience with any of the following: UNIX, Linux, C, C-sharp, C++ Language experience, Script Programming using Python and Perl.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Semiconductor Fabrication and Lithography.<br>Knowledge of EDA (Electronic Design Automation) tools<br>Database Concepts, SQL and hardware platform architecture, networking.<br>Distributed computing and/or multi-threading experience.<br>Information Security protocols.<br>Experience with full-stack web development<br>Benefits at Intel<br>Our total rewards package goes above and beyond just a paycheck. Whether you're looking to build your career, improve your health, or protect your wealth, we offer generous benefits to help you achieve your goals. Go to Intel Benefits | Intel Careers for details of benefits available to you. Intel reserves the right to modify, change or discontinue benefit plans at any time in its sole discretion. <br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Intel Foundry strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art while delighting our customers -- from delivering cutting-edge silicon process and packaging technology leadership for the AI era, enabling our customers to design leadership products, global manufacturing scale and supply chain, through the continuous yield improvements to advanced packaging all the way to final test and assembly.  We ensure our foundry customers' products receive our utmost focus in terms of service, technology enablement and capacity commitments. Employees in the Foundry Technology Manufacturing are part of a worldwide factory network that designs, develops, manufactures, and assembly/test packages the compute devices to improve the lives of every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$91,770.00-$129,560.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Intel Foundry Capital Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Intel-Foundry-Capital-Analyst_JR0277284?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277284<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>The Finance Team supporting Intel Foundry Capital plays a vital role in ensuring the financial stability and efficiency of the foundry operations. This specialized team is responsible for managing the financial aspects of foundry processes, including budgeting, cost analysis, and financial reporting specific to the foundry needs.<br>We are looking a Capital Analyst to join our team, the role’s responsibilities include but are not limited to:<br>Creates and analyzes financial information and business trends to develop reconciliations, financial reports, variance explanations, risk assessments and solutions.<br>Evaluates accounting and reporting and recommends solutions to ensure the integrity of external and internal reporting.<br>Develops annual budgets and forecasts for different business units and departments, as well as for the organization to influence the decision-making process and direction of varying levels of business leaders including project leads, managers, operational business groups and factories.<br>Identifies, performs and drives process improvement opportunities in the monthend close processes and supports management reporting related to operations performance on a monthly, quarterly and annual basis.<br>Prepares and maintains operational budget, forecasts, plan and reports and develops operational workflows that bridge technical and business needs.<br>Makes recommendations around financial process improvements by maintaining financial tools to perform analysis and recommends automation and more efficient methods of creation and delivery.<br>Evaluates capital expenditure requirements and recommends suitable financing options.<br>Develops periodic management reports for performance measurement of different business units and the organization.<br>Provides decision support to leadership by monitoring revenue and costs against the budgets and forecasts and explaining variance through root cause analysis.<br>Supports decision making by providing ad hoc financial and key performance indicator analyzes that influence leadership decision making.<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. This position is not eligible for Intel's immigration sponsorship. <br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>Bachelor's degree or Advance student in Finance, Business Administration, Accounting, or similar field.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>1+ year of related practical experience in financial roles<br>Intermediate Excel for Data Analysis (Managing large sets of data)<br>Knowledge of Power BI<br>Knowledge of SAP<br>          Job Type:<br>College Grad<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Business group:<br>Join Intel's Finance Group, a key player in driving strategic business decisions that enhance shareholder value. Our team is dedicated to facilitating change and improvement across finance and the operations we support. As strategic partners, we lead acquisitions and inorganic growth initiatives, managing transactions from ideation to completion while serving as trusted advisors to executive leadership. We also design and support Intel’s IT infrastructure, driving e-Commerce and web services with a focus on robust security and identity protection. Our innovative supply chain solutions propel Intel’s market initiatives, ensuring seamless support and maximizing revenue opportunities. Additionally, we enhance employee experiences by maintaining Intel sites globally and advancing environmental sustainability efforts.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$68,640.00-$88,520.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will be eligible for our hybrid work model which allows employees to split their time between working on-site at their assigned Intel site and off-site. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Policy Communications Manager]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Washington-DC/Policy-Communications-Manager_JR0277427?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Washington, D.C.<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277427<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Intel's Global Communications and Events team is seeking a dynamic and strategic Policy Communications Manager to lead global policy communications. In this role, you will collaborate closely with Government Affairs and cross-functional teams to develop and execute comprehensive communications strategies that advance Intel's policy objectives, foster trust with our customers and key stakeholders within all branches of the U.S. Federal, State and Local government, as well as governments worldwide.<br>About the role:<br>As the Policy Communications Manager, you will be the voice of Intel's policy perspectives-proactively shaping narratives across traditional, digital, and emerging media channels. Your work will amplify Intel's position on critical policy issues impacting the technology sector, guiding public discourse and reinforcing Intel's leadership in innovation and responsibility.<br>Key responsibilities:<br>Lead proactive communications of Intel's policy positions through traditional, new, and emerging media.<br>Develop clear, compelling external content for policy initiatives, including key messages, Q+As, talking points, press releases, blogs and social media.<br>Manage public policy issues impacting Intel's workforce, business operations, and communities.<br>Handle complex media inquiries related to policy, proactively shaping our agenda, while reactively crafting response strategies and coordinating cross-functional review and approvals.<br>Build and sustain strong relationships with media professionals and influencers that cover the intersection of business, technology, and policy.<br>Drive integrated communications programs for high-profile announcements and policy milestones.<br>Support sales team in crafting and implementing campaigns and messaging to attract U.S. government customers.<br>Collaborate with third-party organizations, such as industry trade groups, to ensure Intel's policy positions are accurately represented.<br>Monitor and analyze policy trends, regulatory changes, and competitive activities to inform communication strategies.<br>What you bring:<br>Exceptional written, verbal, and visual storytelling skills, with the ability to distill complex government, technical, and policy content into compelling stories for diverse audiences.<br>Strong project management with a track record of delivering high-quality work on time and under tight deadlines.<br>Flexible and resilient problem solver with strong consensus building skills and the ability to navigate sensitive situations.<br>A proactive, self-starting mindset with a passion for innovative storytelling and communications.<br>A strategic viewpoint that aligns messaging and business objectives with Intel's government, customer, and policy stakeholders.<br>Deep understanding of political topics related to the technology sector.<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. This position is not eligible for Intel's immigration sponsorship.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>Bachelor's degree in communications, marketing, political science, government affairs or related field.<br>10+ years of experience in government affairs or technology industry communications.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Experience in government communications, Capitol Hill, or U.S. federal administration roles strongly preferred.<br>Previous experience in and strong understanding of the semiconductor industry.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Washington, D.C.<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>The Global Communications and Events Group (GCE) is the dynamic force behind the organization's brand narrative and public engagement, orchestrating impactful communication strategies and world-class events that elevate the company's presence on the global stage. This team crafts compelling messages that resonate with diverse audiences, leveraging digital platforms and media channels to enhance brand visibility and reputation. They are also responsible for designing and executing memorable events that foster meaningful connections and showcase the company's innovations and achievements. GCE offers a vibrant and creative environment where professionals can thrive, surrounded by passionate colleagues who value collaboration and ingenuity.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$133,710.00-$188,760.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will be eligible for our hybrid work model which allows employees to split their time between working on-site at their assigned Intel site and off-site. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Automation Commodity Manager]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Arizona-Phoenix/Automation-Commodity-Manager_JR0276695?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0276695<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>The Global Supply Management - Manufacturing Automation (GSM-MA) team is responsible for Supply Chain Management of factory automation products and services in support of Intel's Technology Development TD and High Volume Manufacturing needs. <br>Responsibilities include but are not limited to:<br>Develops and executes commodity strategies, as well as drives supplier development through innovation and collaboration.<br>Maintains advanced knowledge of industry and market dynamics, and knowledge of commodities to drive supply chain solutions ahead of Intel's needs.<br>Leverages and applies strong understanding of contracting and negotiating, risk mitigation, and supplier relationship management to manage supplier relationships and provide sustainable cost, quality, availability, and technology solutions with adherence to procurement policies.<br>Owns relationships and coordinates purchasing activities with cross functional teams to acquire materials and services in a cost effective and timely manner.<br>Ensures that the respective commodity meets the business demand and cost requirements necessary for Intel to develop great products/services for its customers.<br>Works closely with partner teams and suppliers to define standard and custom product requirements, influence design decisions to meet desired product/service demand and fulfil the business objective.<br>Works with partner teams to capture commodity requirements and understand how design can influence cost and give feedback.<br>Conducts periodic executive reviews of commodity sourcing strategy in partnership with internal teams/customers to shape strategic business objectives and account investments through aligned roadmaps.<br>Reviews and pivots sourcing strategy when required in response to changing market conditions and develops mitigation plans to ensure business continuity.<br>Works closely with finance/legal to resolve disputes with suppliers/internal partners.<br>Leads sustainability and regulatory compliance and ensures suppliers comply with Intel's business processes.<br>Collaborates with internal and external stakeholders to drive supply chain optimization, understand affordability, set cost targets and define cost reduction roadmaps through detailed understanding of supplier's financial targets, business objectives, and margins.<br>#cj<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. Experience listed below would be obtained through a combination of your degree, research and or relevant previous job and or internship experiences.  <br> Minimum Qualifications:<br>Bachelor's degree in supply chain or related field of study.<br>U.S. Citizenship required<br>Ability to obtain and maintain a US Government Security Clearance.<br>5+ years of relevant experience in supply chain, sourcing, and/or related field.<br>3+ years experience with technology hardware and software ecosystem and commercial agreements.<br><br><br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Active US Government Security Clearance, with a minimum of Secret level.<br>Master's degree in supply chain or related field of study.<br>Experience working with factory automation stakeholders.<br>Program Management experience<br><br>           Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>Additional Locations:<br>Business group:<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$120,390.00-$169,960.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Identity Security Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Identity-Security-Analyst_JR0277299-1?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277299<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>The world is transforming - and so is Intel. Intel is a company of bold and curious inventors and problem solvers who create some of the most astounding technology advancements and experiences in the world. With a legacy of relentless innovation and a commitment to bring smart, connected devices to every person on Earth, our diverse and brilliant teams are continually searching for tomorrow's technology and revel in the challenge that changing the world for the better brings. We work every single day to design and manufacture silicon products that empower people's digital lives. Come join us and do something wonderful.<br>Who we Are:<br>Intel's Information Security organization enables Intel to provide secure products, solutions, and services which meet U.S. regulatory requirements. The Information Security organization supports the unique IT information Security and Compliance requirements for Intel Federal projects that deliver products and/or services to the US Government (USG).As part of this team, you will help us grow our secure solution suite to meet U.S. Government requirements. The Intel Information Security organization is seeking a Network Security Engineer. The candidate chosen for this role will assist senior engineers with design, architecture, and build of secure classified network products to support USG operations.<br>Primary duties and responsibilities:<br>Assist with architecting identity and identity security products in secured enclaves, including product testing, validation, and selection.<br>Assist with design and long-term roadmap planning for new and future scalability in secure enclaves.<br>Coordinate security assessments to identify security control failures and recommend corrective actions.<br>Development and configuration experience of various SailPoint IIQ modules (e.g. audit, compliance, lifecycle, service account, Microsoft Active Directory connector).<br>Design and integration of Microsoft Active Directory.<br>Design and deploy custom forms, approval workflows, connections in SailPoint for access requests, access certifications, and provisioning.<br>Automate processes in the SailPoint toolset using PowerShell scripting.<br>Business travel is required as needed.<br>Ability to thrive in dynamic and fast-paced environments.<br>Excellent communication, leadership, strong troubleshooting, debugging, and analytical skills.<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. Experience listed below would be obtained through a combination of your degree, research and or relevant previous job and or internship experiences.  <br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>US Citizenship required<br>Ability to obtain and maintain a US Government Security Clearance<br>High School /Equivalent Diploma and 3+ years of applicable experience with at least one of the following certifications: CISSP, CISM, CASP E, Security+ OR Bachelor's degree and 2+ years of applicable experience<br>2+ years' experience configuring Access Profiles, Roles, and Identity Profiles<br>2+ years' experience in Active Directory<br>2+ years' experience in APIs (RESTful services preferred)<br>1+ years' experience in implementing and supporting SailPoint IIQ modules like Compliance Manager, Lifecycle Manager, Integration modules, in both production and nonproduction environments<br>1+ years' experience in designing and implementing custom SailPoint solutions<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Active US Government Top Secret (TS) Security Clearance with the ability to obtain and maintain SCI access<br>Bachelor's degree in Systems Engineering, Cyber Security Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, Information Systems, or similar discipline and four years of work-related experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience<br>Experience with DoD security implementation (e.g. STIG) and security tools for managing the environment<br>Experience with business continuity and disaster recovery<br>Experience with scripting in the Windows and UNIX environment<br>Experience with Microsoft SQL Server 2019/2022<br>Experience with Web Tech: HTML, JavaScript, JSP, XML, XSL, and DTD<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix, US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Business group:<br>Join Intel's Finance Group, a key player in driving strategic business decisions that enhance shareholder value. Our team is dedicated to facilitating change and improvement across finance and the operations we support. As strategic partners, we lead acquisitions and inorganic growth initiatives, managing transactions from ideation to completion while serving as trusted advisors to executive leadership. We also design and support Intel’s IT infrastructure, driving e-Commerce and web services with a focus on robust security and identity protection. Our innovative supply chain solutions propel Intel’s market initiatives, ensuring seamless support and maximizing revenue opportunities. Additionally, we enhance employee experiences by maintaining Intel sites globally and advancing environmental sustainability efforts.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$117,270.00-$165,550.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Identity Security Analyst]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Identity-Security-Analyst_JR0277301?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0277301<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>The world is transforming - and so is Intel. Intel is a company of bold and curious inventors and problem solvers who create some of the most astounding technology advancements and experiences in the world. With a legacy of relentless innovation and a commitment to bring smart, connected devices to every person on Earth, our diverse and brilliant teams are continually searching for tomorrow's technology and revel in the challenge that changing the world for the better brings.<br>We work every single day to design and manufacture silicon products that empower people's digital lives. Come join us and do something wonderful. Who we Are: Intel's Information Security organization enables Intel to provide secure products, solutions, and services which meet U.S. regulatory requirements. The Information Security organization supports the unique IT information Security and Compliance requirements for Intel Federal projects that deliver products and/or services to the US Government (USG).<br>As part of this team, you will help us grow our secure solution suite to meet U.S. Government requirements. The Intel Information Security organization is seeking a Network Security Engineer. The candidate chosen for this role will assist senior engineers with design, architecture, and build of secure classified network products to support USG operations.<br><br>Primary duties and responsibilities:<br>Design, deploy, and manage enterprise-grade PKI solutions.<br>Lead certificate lifecycle management efforts using EJBCA.<br>Automate PKI-related tasks and processes.<br>Collaborate with security, infrastructure, and DevOps teams to integrate PKI solutions with various platforms and applications.<br>Develop and enforce policies, standards, and best practices for certificate issuance, renewal, and revocation.<br>Monitor PKI infrastructure health, availability, and compliance with internal and regulatory requirements.<br>Troubleshoot PKI-related issues including certificate chain validation, CRL/OCSP configurations, and encryption/signing issues.<br>Provide documentation, technical guidance, and training to internal teams.<br>Business travel is required as needed.<br>Ability to thrive in dynamic and fast-paced environments<br>Qualifications:<br>You must possess the below minimum qualifications to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates. Experience listed below would be obtained through a combination of your degree, research and or relevant previous job and or internship experiences.<br>Minimum Qualifications:<br>US Citizenship required Ability to obtain and maintain a US Government Security Clearance<br>High School /Equivalent Diploma and 3+ years of applicable experience with at least one of the following security certifications: CISSP, CEH, SSCP OR Bachelor's degree and 2+ years of applicable experience.<br>2+ years' experience configuring Access Profiles, Roles, and Identity Profiles<br>2+ years' experience in Active Directory<br>2+ years' experience in APIs (RESTful services preferred)<br>1+ years' experience in implementing and supporting SailPoint IIQ modules like Compliance Manager, Lifecycle Manager, Integration modules, in both production and nonproduction environments<br>1+ years' experience in designing and implementing custom SailPoint solutions<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Active US Government Top Secret (TS) Security Clearance with the ability to obtain and maintain SCI access Bachelor's degree in Systems Engineering, Cyber Security Engineering, Computer Engineering, Computer Science, Information Systems, or similar discipline and four years of work-related experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience<br>Experience with DoD security implementation (e.g. STIG) and security tools for managing the environment<br>Experience with business continuity and disaster recovery<br>Experience with scripting in the Windows and UNIX environment<br>Experience with Microsoft SQL Server 2019/2022Experience with Web Tech: HTML, JavaScript, JSP, XML, XSL, and DTD<br>Requirements listed would be obtained through a combination of industry relevant job experience, internship experiences and or schoolwork/classes/research.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix, US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Business group:<br>Join Intel's Finance Group, a key player in driving strategic business decisions that enhance shareholder value. Our team is dedicated to facilitating change and improvement across finance and the operations we support. As strategic partners, we lead acquisitions and inorganic growth initiatives, managing transactions from ideation to completion while serving as trusted advisors to executive leadership. We also design and support Intel’s IT infrastructure, driving e-Commerce and web services with a focus on robust security and identity protection. Our innovative supply chain solutions propel Intel’s market initiatives, ensuring seamless support and maximizing revenue opportunities. Additionally, we enhance employee experiences by maintaining Intel sites globally and advancing environmental sustainability efforts.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$117,270.00-$165,550.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will require an on-site presence. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Marvell: Senior Staff Firmware Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://marvell.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MarvellCareers/job/Santa-Clara-CA/Senior-Staff-Firmware-Engineer_2502816?timeType=8d835e03b09d01f4765c6667aa117200&workerSubType=65dea26481d00180af95ab4927173219&Country=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&jobFamilyGroup=65dea26481d0011d9f4e14dd98175801&jobFamilyGroup=65dea26481d0016bd6c014dd98175a01&jobFamilyGroup=65dea26481d001fb93160edd98173001&jobFamilyGroup=65dea26481d001a762a312dd98174e01]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Santa Clara, CA<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>2502816<br>About Marvell <br>Marvell’s semiconductor solutions are the essential building blocks of the data infrastructure that connects our world. Across enterprise, cloud and AI, automotive, and carrier architectures, our innovative technology is enabling new possibilities. <br>At Marvell, you can affect the arc of individual lives, lift the trajectory of entire industries, and fuel the transformative potential of tomorrow. For those looking to make their mark on purposeful and enduring innovation, above and beyond fleeting trends, Marvell is a place to thrive, learn, and lead. <br>Your Team, Your Impact<br>Marvell: Powering the Future of AI Infrastructure<br><br>Marvell delivers breakthrough technologies that enable the world’s leading data infrastructure solutions. Our portfolio spans ultra-fast read channels, high-performance processors, advanced transceivers, efficient analog designs, and robust cryptographic engines. These innovations support a wide range of applications—from HDD and SSD electronics to comprehensive system solutions powering PCs, servers, cloud platforms, and enterprise environments.<br><br>For over 30 years, Marvell has been a trusted partner to the world’s top technology companies. We move, store, process, and secure data through semiconductor solutions tailored to meet today’s demands and tomorrow’s ambitions. Built on a foundation of deep customer collaboration and transparency, our approach is reshaping the future of enterprise, cloud, automotive, and carrier architectures—driving transformation for the better.<br><br>Marvell is a leading provider of innovative technologies, including ultra-fast read channels, high-performance processors, leading edge transceivers, highly efficient analog designs, and powerful cryptographic engines. These solutions address all segments of the hard disk drive (HDD) and solid-state drive (SSD) electronics markets, providing complete solutions including controllers, product firmware, and reference board designs. Many of the same technologies have been utilized in Marvell system solutions products, powering PCs, servers, cloud, and enterprise systems.<br>What You Can Expect<br>Responsibilities<br>• Architect, design and develop firmware for reliable, scalable, high performing SERDES/PCIE IPs using C/C++.<br>• Develop new features and enhance existing features for AI infrastructure connecting products by designing firmware and algorithms tailored for Marvell mixed signal hardware-based accelerators.<br>• Develop software and troubleshoot issues related to hardware bring-up, multi-threaded software development with virtualized hardware.<br>• Work with application engineers (AE), product managers and cross functional hardware/software engineers to investigate and solve customer issues.<br>• Analyze and investigate methods to enhance firmware performance on Marvell SoC/IP by using existing hardware and simulators and suggest future hardware/software design improvements.<br>• Plan, schedule, estimate efforts for projects and provide technical guidance to junior engineers during execution.<br>• Work on MCU based SERDES/PCIe products, design and develop firmware and software for networking and switching products.<br>What We're Looking For<br>• BS / MS in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science or related fields and 5-10 years of related professional experience with:<br>o C/C++<br>o RTOS or Scheduler<br>o Microcontroller embedded firmware with mixed signal products<br>o Hardware bring-up on microcontroller with IDE through JTAG, SW<br>o SERDES/PCIE protocol familiarity<br>o Github and Jira familiarity<br>o Python is a plus<br> o Github Copilot is a plus<br>Expected Base Pay Range (USD)<br>124,420 - 186,400, $ per annum<br>The successful candidate’s starting base pay will be determined based on job-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location and market conditions. The expected base pay range for this role may be modified based on market conditions.<br>Additional Compensation and Benefit Elements <br>At Marvell, we offer a total compensation package with a base, bonus and equity.Health and financial wellbeing are part of the package. That means flexible time off, 401k, plus a year-end shutdown, floating holidays, paid time off to volunteer. Have a question about our benefits packages - health or financial? Ask your recruiter during the interview process.<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, gender identity, disability or protected veteran status.<br>Any applicant who requires a reasonable accommodation during the selection process should contact Marvell HR Helpdesk at TAOps@marvell.com.<br>Interview Integrity<br> As part of our commitment to fair and authentic hiring practices, we ask that candidates do not use AI tools (e.g., transcription apps, real-time answer generators like ChatGPT, CoPilot, or note-taking bots) during interviews.<br> <br>Our interviews are designed to assess your personal experience, thought process, and communication skills in real-time. If a candidate uses such tools during an interview, they will be disqualified from the hiring process.<br>This position may require access to technology and/or software subject to U.S. export control laws and regulations, including the Export Administration Regulations (EAR). As such, applicants must be eligible to access export-controlled information as defined under applicable law. Marvell may be required to obtain export licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce and/or the U.S. Department of State. Except for U.S. citizens, lawful permanent residents, or protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), all applicants may be subject to an export license review process prior to employment.<br>#LI-TT1]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Principal AI Engineer, Intelligent Sensors]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-CA-San-Jose-Rio-Robles/Principal-AI-Engineer--Intelligent-Sensors_R255778?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, CA, San Jose, Rio Robles<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R255778<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          Principal AI Engineer, Intelligent Sensors <br>Role Overview: <br>The Edge AI team is seeking a Principal AI Engineer to lead the development of innovative AI solutions for intelligent sensors that enable real-time decision-making in constrained environments. This role focuses on designing and implementing next-generation AI building blocks co-designed with novel sensors that can operate reliably on resource-limited hardware, leveraging optimization techniques and advanced AI methodologies. The ideal candidate will have a strong background in both hardware design and hardware-aware AI models and the ability to lead major technical initiatives while collaborating with cross-functional teams. <br>Key Responsibilities: <br>Drive the development of AI-enabled intelligent sensors in conjunction with our sensor and digital hardware teams. <br>Couple new hardware architectures or sensing techniques with physics-aware AI models. <br>Lead efforts in hardware-aware AI optimization to achieve efficient and scalable solutions. <br>Take part and lead the AI aspect of hardware/AI codesigns with adjacent teams. <br>Support the creation of reusable AI building blocks for intelligent sensors, ensuring scalability and adaptability across applications. <br>Provide technical leadership and mentorship to junior engineers, fostering innovation and collaboration. <br>Stay current on advancements in AI, edge computing, and sensor technologies, applying state-of-the-art techniques to solve challenging problems. <br>Qualifications: <br>Master’s degree or equivalent experience. <br>8+ years of industry experience in AI/ML model development, optimization, and deployment. <br>Deep expertise in sensing, analog, or hardware technologies, with hands-on experience. <br>Demonstrated leadership of technologies or teams to develop cutting edge solutions touching hardware, software, and AI. <br>Strong understanding of hardware-aware AI, including benchmarking and performance evaluation on embedded platforms. <br>Proficiency in Python, C++, and modern AI frameworks (e.g., TensorFlow, PyTorch, ONNX). <br>Ability to lead technical projects and collaborate effectively across multidisciplinary teams. <br>Preferred Skills: <br>Experience with sensor fusion, perception, and decision-making systems. <br>Familiarity with designing custom AI architectures for edge devices with tight compute and power constraints. <br>Knowledge of Analog Devices hardware platforms or similar embedded ecosystems. <br>Strong communication and leadership skills, with a track record of mentoring and growing engineering talent. <br> For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>The expected wage range for a new hire into this position is $170,775 to $256,163.<br>Actual wage offered may vary depending on work location, experience, education, training, external market data, internal pay equity, or other bona fide factors.<br>This position qualifies for a discretionary performance-based bonus which is based on personal and company factors.<br>This position includes medical, vision and dental coverage, 401k, paid vacation, holidays, and sick time, and other benefits.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Principal Engineer – Time-Series Foundation Models]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-CA-San-Jose-Rio-Robles/Principal-Engineer---Time-Series-Foundation-Models_R255906?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, CA, San Jose, Rio Robles<br>US, MA, Boston<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R255906<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          Principal Engineer – Time-Series Foundation Models  <br><br>About Lorenz Labs<br>Lorenz Labs, ADI’s advanced AI research group, is chartered to pioneer the frontier of Physical Intelligence—developing foundation models and agentic systems that reason about the physical world. We are building the next generation of models that go beyond language and vision, into time, signals, and embodied experience.<br>About the Role<br>We are seeking a Principal Engineer in Time-Series Foundation Models to lead research and development of large-scale time-series AI models. This role will drive innovation similar to Archetype AI’s sensor-based foundation modeling, but with ADI’s unique advantage at the intersection of sensors, signals, and edge compute.<br><br>You will develop and scale models that unify temporal, spatial, and multimodal signals into foundation architectures for anomaly detection, forecasting, and reasoning across physical domains (e.g., industrial, energy, health, robotics). This position combines cutting-edge research, technical leadership, and cross-functional collaboration with ADI’s sensor, semiconductor, and systems teams.<br><br><br>Key Responsibilities<br>Lead the design and training of time-series foundation models, including transformers, diffusion, and hybrid neuro-symbolic architectures.<br>Explore cross-domain generalization: from network telemetry to biosignals, from manufacturing logs to multimodal sensor data.<br>Develop new methods for anomaly detection, causal inference, motif discovery, and representation learning in high-dimensional time-series.<br>Partner with ADI hardware, signal processing, and edge compute teams to optimize models for deployment in resource-constrained, real-time environments.<br>Publish at top conferences (NeurIPS, ICLR, ICML, KDD, AISTATS) to establish ADI as a thought leader in time-series AI.<br>Collaborate with internal and external partners (universities, research labs, startups) to accelerate innovation.<br>Mentor junior scientists and help shape Lorenz Labs’ research agenda on physical intelligence.<br><br>Must Have Skills<br>Deep expertise in time-series ML, including statistical, deep learning, and foundation models (Chronos, TimesFM, TimeGPT).<br>Strong background in optimization, control theory, Gaussian Processes, and anomaly detection.<br>Track record of industrial research with patents and publications in ML/AI.<br>Proficiency in Python and ML frameworks (PyTorch, TensorFlow, HuggingFace, etc.), with experience in large-scale training pipelines.<br>Ability to collaborate across disciplines—ML, hardware, embedded systems, data engineering—and translate research into deployable systems.<br><br>Preferred Education and Experience<br>PhD in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, Applied Math, or related field.<br>10+ years of experience in ML research and development (academic + industrial).<br>Demonstrated success in leading research-to-product transitions.<br>Recognized contributions to the ML community (publications, patents, open-source).<br><br>Why You’ll Love Working at ADI<br>At Lorenz Labs, you will work at the edge of AI, sensors, and the physical world. You’ll have the freedom to explore new paradigms of modeling time and signals, backed by ADI’s scale, data access, and hardware ecosystem. This is an opportunity to shape a new category of AI research—foundation models for the physical world—and help build the future of PhysGPT and the 'Artificial Engineer.'<br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>The expected wage range for a new hire into this position is $170,775 to $256,163.<br>Actual wage offered may vary depending on work location, experience, education, training, external market data, internal pay equity, or other bona fide factors.<br>This position qualifies for a discretionary performance-based bonus which is based on personal and company factors.<br>This position includes medical, vision and dental coverage, 401k, paid vacation, holidays, and sick time, and other benefits.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Director, Systems Design/Architecture Engineering]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Canada-Ottawa/Director--Systems-Design-Architecture-Engineering_R253820?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Canada, Ottawa<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R253820<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          Director of Systems Engineering – High Voltage & Protection (Datacenter & Energy BU)<br>Reports to: General Manager, High Voltage & Protection Business Unit<br>Key Responsibilities<br>Lead system architecture and platform development for high-voltage power conversion and protection in datacenter applications.<br>Drive innovation in 400V and 800V architectures, enabling scalable, high-efficiency power delivery for next-gen computing.<br>Define and execute system-level roadmaps aligned with market trends, customer needs, and ADI’s strategic goals.<br>Oversee module development, including electrical, thermal, and mechanical integration for DC/DC controllers, power stages, wide bandgap (GaN and SiC) and protection solutions ensuring high efficiency, power density, and system reliability.<br>Provide technical leadership in isolated power and magnetics design, ensuring performance, safety, and EMI compliance.<br>Develop and implement high voltage and protection strategies, including hotswap, eFuse, DC/DC controllers, power stages and wide bandgap (GaN and SiC) solutions.<br>Build, lead, and scale a world-class systems engineering team, attracting top talent and fostering a culture of innovation and collaboration.<br>Collaborate cross-functionally with silicon, firmware, and software teams to deliver complete, validated solutions.<br>Engage with customers and industry bodies, translating system challenges into product requirements and influencing standards.<br>Required Skills & Experience<br>10+ years of experience in power systems, with a focus on high-voltage (400V–800V) and isolated power architectures.<br>Expertise in isolated power design, including transformer-based topologies, controllers, powerstages & wide bandgap (GaN and SiC) technologies.<br>Strong background in magnetics design, including custom magnetics, core material selection, and EMI optimization.<br>Hands-on experience in DC/DC and protection technologies, including hotswap controllers and eFuses.<br>Proven experience in power module development, including mechanical, thermal, and electrical integration for high-reliability systems.<br>Demonstrated success in building and leading technical teams, including hiring, mentoring, and performance management.<br>Leadership in system-level architecture, integration, and validation of power conversion systems.<br>Experience with AC-DC and DC-DC topologies, including resonant, LLC, phase-shifted full-bridge, and multi-phase buck.<br>Familiarity with digital control, firmware integration, and model-based design tools (e.g., MATLAB/Simulink, PLECS).<br>Strong understanding of datacenter power delivery trends, including 48V, 400V, and 800V ecosystems, and hands-on experience with wide bandgap technologies such as GaN and SiC for high-efficiency, high-density power designs.<br>Excellent communication and collaboration skills, with experience engaging customers, partners, and cross-functional teams.<br>Experience in regulatory compliance, including IEC, UL, and regional safety and EMC standards.<br>Advanced degree in Electrical Engineering or related field preferred; PhD or MBA is a plus.<br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>Accessibility for Ontarians with Disabilities Act (AODA): Analog Devices Canada Ltd. has a process in place and provides accommodations for employees with disabilities. To request an accommodation, please contact Connections HR Services at 781-937-2500 or at ConnectionsHRServices@analog.com.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Staff Research Scientist, Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-MA-Boston/Staff-Research-Scientist--Artificial-Intelligence_R255394?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, MA, Boston<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R255394<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          Job Title: Staff Research Scientist, Artificial Intelligence <br> About Analog Devices: Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies to drive advancements in smart factories, mobility, healthcare, climate solutions, and reliable connectivity. With revenue exceeding $9 billion in FY24 and around 26,000 employees globally working alongside 125,000 global customers, ADI ensures today’s innovators stay Ahead of What’s Possible. <br> The Analog Garage: Located in the heart of downtown Boston, the Analog Garage is ADI’s Research and Advanced Development Center, empowering the company by pioneering breakthrough technologies. The Algorithmic Solutions Group within the Analog Garage researches and develops cutting-edge, efficient algorithms to convert data into intelligence that addresses society’s most pressing challenges. The team’s expertise spans fields such as machine learning, artificial intelligence, signal processing, computer vision, computational linguistics, communication systems, and other areas of electrical engineering and computer science, creating solutions with real-world impact. <br> Job opportunity: The Algorithmic Solutions Group is seeking a motivated researcher to develop innovative solutions at the intersection of cutting-edge AI algorithms and ADI technologies. In this role, you will: <br>Collaborate within a multidisciplinary team of researchers, engineers, and domain experts to bridge AI innovation with practical solutions <br>Develop cutting-edge AI algorithms designed for resource-constrained environments <br>Prototype and validate solutions, using both software simulations and hands-on hardware, to demonstrate feasibility and performance <br>Stay abreast of state-of-the-art algorithms and research advances in areas relevant to Analog Devices. <br> Qualifications: <br>PhD degree in Electical Engineering, Computer Science or related fields. <br>Experience in two or more of the following areas: <br>Developing, deploying, and optimizing AI models using frameworks and tools such as PyTorch, TensorFlow, and cloud-based AI platforms <br>Modern AI architectures and training paradigms <br>Deploying and optimizing models on constrained hardware using techniques such as quantization, pruning, distillation, or on-device retraining <br>Computer architecture, AI accelerators, and/or model compilation <br>Analog, mixed-signal, and/or RF circuit design <br>  Preferred qualifications: <br>3+ years of industry experience developing and deploying machine learning models <br>Strong publication record in top conferences and/or journals <br> Why join Us? By joining ADI, you’ll have the opportunity to work at the intersection of hardware and AI to bring intelligence to the edge and create solutions that have a profound impact. Enjoy a dynamic work environment, be part of a team that values diversity of thought and experience and take your career to the next level. <br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>The expected wage range for a new hire into this position is $166,800 to $229,350.<br>Actual wage offered may vary depending on work location, experience, education, training, external market data, internal pay equity, or other bona fide factors.<br>This position qualifies for a discretionary performance-based bonus which is based on personal and company factors.<br>This position includes medical, vision and dental coverage, 401k, paid vacation, holidays, and sick time, and other benefits.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Staff Digital Chip Architect and Digital Systems Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-NC-Durham/Staff-Digital-Chip-Architect-and-Digital-Systems-Engineer_R255041-1?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, NC, Durham<br>US, MA, Wilmington<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R255041<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          We are seeking an experienced and technically exceptional Staff Engineer in DSP and Digital Systems Chip Architect to join a small, high-performing team of engineers focused on the architecture and development of cutting-edge mixed-signal and software-defined radio (SDR) integrated circuits. This role is ideal for a hands-on technical contributor with a deep background in digital signal processing and digital design, and a passion for shaping definition, requirements and solutions in a collaborative team.  DSP and Digital System Architects work across 50-100 engineer, cross-functional development teams to specify and guide digital, firmware, software and processor subsystem requirements and architecture. <br>Key Responsibilities<br>Architectural Leadership: Drive the definition and architecture of complex mixed-signal ICs and SDR chips, with a focus on digital accelerators and subsystems.<br>Cross-Functional Collaboration: Work closely with analog, RF, firmware, and software teams to ensure cohesive SoC and system-level design.<br>Project Execution: Support the successful execution of multiple chip development programs from concept through tape-out and validation. <br>Mentorship and Culture: Foster a culture of technical excellence and continuous learning.  Support the development of team members through mentoring and engagement.<br>Innovation and Strategy: Stay ahead of industry trends and emerging technologies to guide architectural decisions and maintain competitive advantage.<br>External Engagement: Work with Customers, Ecosystem Partners, and ADI stakeholders to define future SDR technologies.<br>Required Qualifications<br>10+ years of experience in digital IC design, with a strong history of delivering complex mixed-signal or SDR chips.<br>Deep expertise in digital signal processing, RTL design, and digital architecture.<br>Strong knowledge of:<br>Firmware and embedded software<br>Radio architecture and signal chains<br>High-speed ADCs/DACs<br>SerDes and high-speed interfaces<br>Microprocessor subsystems and digital accelerators<br>DSP cores and custom compute architecture<br>Hardware/Software Co-Design and Digital Modelling<br>Preferred Qualifications<br>Experience with system-level modeling and simulation (e.g., MATLAB, SystemVerilog, Python).<br>Demonstrated ability of requirements capture and documentation.<br>Familiarity with SoC integration and verification methodologies.<br>Exposure to productization and manufacturing ICs in high-volume.<br>Strong written and verbal communication skills.<br>Why Join Us?<br>This is a rare opportunity to shape the future of advanced digital and mixed-signal systems in a role that blends deep technical engagement with systems thinking. You’ll work with a passionate team on impactful technologies in a collaborative and innovative environment.  For a survey of the types of devices we build, check out AD9084 (wideband MxFE), ADRV9040 (RF Transceiver), ADRV9003 (narrowband RF transceiver) on www.analog.com.<br>Schedule<br>: Full-time<br>Education Level<br>: MSEE / PhD<br>Employee Status<br>: Regular<br>Travel<br>: Yes, 10% of the time.<br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>The expected wage range for a new hire into this position is $125,250 to $187,875.<br>Actual wage offered may vary depending on work location, experience, education, training, external market data, internal pay equity, or other bona fide factors.<br>This position qualifies for a discretionary performance-based bonus which is based on personal and company factors.<br>This position includes medical, vision and dental coverage, 401k, paid vacation, holidays, and sick time, and other benefits.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Staff Engineer, Systems Embedded Design Engineering]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-MA-Boston/Staff-Engineer--Systems-Software-Design-Engineering_R244946?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, MA, Boston<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R244946<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          The Analog Garage is ADI’s internal innovation lab, empowering ADI by creating breakthrough technologies. Bringing together engineers, research scientists, and business leaders, we develop new technologies and solutions in a fast-moving, experiment-focused startup atmosphere. As a leader in cutting-edge technology for over 50 years, Analog Devices has a history of performance and the agility to engineer future breakthroughs.<br>The Platform and Systems Team (PST), part of Analog Garage, works cross-functionally with research scientists and other domain experts to advance applications in biotech, renewable energy, autonomous systems, automotive, and many more types of intelligent edge systems. We are seeking a highly skilled and experienced, Staff Embedded Software Engineer. This engineer will play a key role in driving innovation and developing technical solutions for embedded system-level challenges. If you have a strong foundation with very good experience in embedded software development, we want to hear from you!<br>Responsibilities<br>Design and maintain firmware for real-time systems, ensuring quality and performance.<br>Collaborate on requirements, architecture, and deliverables while optimizing with hardware engineers.<br>Test, debug, and integrate complex systems.<br>Assess and adopt new technologies to enhance the team, mentor peers, and ensure seamless collaboration.<br>Required Qualifications<br>BS or MS in EE, ECE, or CS with 8-10 years of experience in embedded firmware/software development.<br>Proficient in software-hardware integration, silicon and board bring-up and validation.<br>Strong verbal and written communication skills; team player that takes responsibility.<br>Highly skilled in C, C++, Rust, and Python or other scripting languages, with experience using build systems like CMake or Cargo.<br>Fluent with RTOS such as FreeRTOS, ZephyrRTOS or Micrium on MCUs.<br>Proficient in software development life cycle management tools like Git and CI/CD, deployment and packaging environments.<br>Good understanding of RISC architectures, including RISC-V and ARM uCs and bus architectures.<br>Experience in developing/troubleshooting low-level drivers and hardware integration for interfaces such as I2C, SPI, UART, USB, Ethernet etc.<br>Desired Qualifications<br>Familiar with Embedded Linux design patterns<br>Experience in heterogenous (FPGA + MCU) system development and deployment<br>Familiarity with digital design (RTL/Verilog) in implementing signal processing chains and other hw accelerator<br>Familiarity with AI/ML edge inference frameworks, quantization, and deployment.<br>Basic knowledge of DSP and sampling theory<br>Basic knowledge of PCB design, reading schematics<br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>The expected wage range for a new hire into this position is $125,250 to $187,875.<br>Actual wage offered may vary depending on work location, experience, education, training, external market data, internal pay equity, or other bona fide factors.<br>This position qualifies for a discretionary performance-based bonus which is based on personal and company factors.<br>This position includes medical, vision and dental coverage, 401k, paid vacation, holidays, and sick time, and other benefits.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ciena: Hardware Test Automation Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://ciena.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Careers/job/Petaluma/Hardware-Test-Automation-Engineer_R028884?Job_Application_ID=JOB_APPLICATION-3-1150225&Location_Country=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&Location_Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&workerSubType=ac99acc6fb6b108fe664fb350ba7ae78&jobFamilyGroup=f08e25a5d78010903df730510aefa016]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Petaluma<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R028884<br>As the global leader in high-speed connectivity, Ciena is committed to a people-first approach. Our teams enjoy a culture focused on prioritizing a flexible work environment that empowers individual growth, well-being, and belonging. We’re a technology company that leads with our humanity—driving our business priorities alongside meaningful social, community, and societal impact.<br>Are you passionate about advancing cutting-edge networking, routing, and Passive Optical Networking (PON) technologies? At Ciena, we are pushing the boundaries of innovation in Passive Optical Networking, Flexible Ethernet, Segment Routing, and virtualized, microservices-oriented architectures. Join us as a Test Automation Engineer and be a key contributor to delivering high-quality, functionally excellent products that define the future of advanced networking services.<br>How You Will Contribute:<br>Design and implement test coverage, automation, validation, and documentation strategies to ensure product excellence.<br>Develop Python-based automation frameworks to test networking features.<br>Debug software and hardware issues, including FPGA debugging.<br>Collaborate with development and technology leaders to ensure comprehensive cross-component QA strategy and coverage.<br>Review and provide feedback on functional specifications, technical requirements, and test plans to champion customer and quality advocacy.<br>Troubleshoot and identify defects, working closely with cross-functional teams and software design experts.<br>The Must Haves:<br>Bachelor’s degree in computer science, engineering, or a related discipline (or equivalent experience).<br>3-5 years of experience in automation testing and hardware debugging.<br>Strong programming expertise in Python for test automation and Verilog RTL.<br>Experience with Intel/Altera FPGA devkits (Agilex 7: I-series and F-series), oscilloscopes, and lab networking (Ethernet (L2) protocols, IP networks, Routing Protocols).<br>Proficiency in Quartus for RTL synthesis, placement, and routing into FPGA designs.<br>Skills in Questa for RTL simulation to debug waveforms.<br>Solid understanding of Passive Optical Networking (PON).<br>Knowledge of Linux development and debugging, specifically in Ubuntu 22.04 and Ubuntu 24.04 environments.<br>Experience with tools such as Jenkins, Git, JIRA, Bitbucket, TestRail, and Pycharm.<br>Excellent verbal and written communication skills.<br>Nice to Haves:<br>Familiarity with product cycles and deployment journeys for carrier-class products in Service Provider environments.<br>Proficiency in Microsoft productivity suite.<br>Pay Range:<br>The salary range for this role in CA is $98, 000 - $156, 600<br>Join Ciena and be part of a team shaping the future of networking technologies!<br>Pay ranges at Ciena are designed to accommodate variations in knowledge, skills, experience, market conditions, and locations, reflecting our diverse products, industries, and lines of business. Please note that the pay range information provided in this posting pertains specifically to the primary location, which is the top location listed in case multiple locations are available.<br>Non-Sales employees may be eligible for a discretionary incentive bonus, while Sales employees may be eligible for a sales commission. In addition to competitive compensation, Ciena offers a comprehensive benefits package, including medical, dental, and vision plans, participation in 401(K) (USA) & DCPP (Canada) with company matching, Employee Stock Purchase Program (ESPP), Employee Assistance Program (EAP), company-paid holidays, paid sick leave, and vacation time. We also comply with all applicable laws regarding Paid Family Leave and other leaves of absence.<br>Not ready to apply? Join our Talent Community to get relevant job alerts straight to your inbox.<br><br>At Ciena, we are committed to building and fostering an environment in which our employees feel respected, valued, and heard.  Ciena values the diversity of its workforce and respects its employees as individuals. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination.<br>Ciena is an Equal Opportunity Employer, including disability and protected veteran status.<br>If contacted in relation to a job opportunity, please advise Ciena of any accommodation measures you may require.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ciena: Embedded System Developer- Optical]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://ciena.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Careers/job/Ottawa/WaveLogic-Technologies-Field-Applications-Engineer_R026772?Job_Application_ID=JOB_APPLICATION-3-1150225&Location_Country=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&Location_Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&workerSubType=ac99acc6fb6b108fe664fb350ba7ae78&jobFamilyGroup=f08e25a5d78010903df730510aefa016]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Ottawa<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R026772<br>As the global leader in high-speed connectivity, Ciena is committed to a people-first approach. Our teams enjoy a culture focused on prioritizing a flexible work environment that empowers individual growth, well-being, and belonging. We’re a technology company that leads with our humanity—driving our business priorities alongside meaningful social, community, and societal impact.<br>Embedded System Developer- Optical is a direct customer-facing role providing customers with strong technical support in Ciena’s optical module and components business. This role has regular, direct customer exposure & contact to all the major global content providers. You will have the opportunity to understand their applications, and build lasting relationships.<br>How You Will Contribute:<br>Ciena’s WaveLogic Technologies modules and components business is an exciting opportunity to diversify and expand Ciena’s addressable market by making its industry-leading coherent optical module technology and components available to a wider range of industry participants, gaining greater access to new geographies and addressing new market segments.<br>As a Field Applications Engineer with a specific interest in embedded software, you will be a key contributor to the team, working closely with our Product Line Managers (PLM) and R&D teams to bring our technology into customer products. In addition to exciting technical challenges, you will gain insight into the business aspects of what we do. In this role you will represent Ciena, so competency and professionalism are paramount.<br>You will…<br>· Work with PLM to provide technical leadership and guidance, with a focus on design wins. You will need to describe in-depth our technology solutions (modules and/or components) to our customers, followed by technical expertise in integrating these solutions into our customers products.<br>· Create software reference designs (API suites) to enable our customers to quickly integrate our technology.<br>· Drive regular working-level meetings with customer engineers, capturing new issues or questions, and ensure issue follow-up and resolution.<br>· Provide customer on-site support, when required, to quickly resolve integration issues.<br>· Create and drive product demos or evaluation boards at industry trade-show events or customer labs.<br>· Execute lab tests when necessary to reproduce customer issues.<br>· Work closely with Ciena R&D to develop, based on analysis of customer needs, requirements that enhance our modules and components.<br>The Must Haves:<br>· 10+ years experience in embedded software and API development (in any area, such as hardware, software, firmware, DSP, serdes), with direct experience in system integration.<br>· Strong knowledge of the underlying components used in the design of optical modules (lasers, DSPs, TIAs, optical receivers, etc).<br>· Experience with high-speed DSP-based electrical serdes architecture, design and/or applications.<br>Assets:<br>· Direct customer-facing experience, with a strong customer-oriented attitude and behavior. Our customers are essential to our business, and deserve to always be treated with respect, professionalism and responsiveness.<br>· Excellent problem-solving and analytical skills, shown through first-product bring-up.<br>· Strong communication and teamwork skills.<br>· Experience authoring datasheets and/or application notes.<br>Pay Range:<br>The annual pay range for this position is $89,400 - $142,800 CAD<br>#LI-WH1<br>Pay ranges at Ciena are designed to accommodate variations in knowledge, skills, experience, market conditions, and locations, reflecting our diverse products, industries, and lines of business. Please note that the pay range information provided in this posting pertains specifically to the primary location, which is the top location listed in case multiple locations are available.<br>Non-Sales employees may be eligible for a discretionary incentive bonus, while Sales employees may be eligible for a sales commission. In addition to competitive compensation, Ciena offers a comprehensive benefits package, including medical, dental, and vision plans, participation in 401(K) (USA) & DCPP (Canada) with company matching, Employee Stock Purchase Program (ESPP), Employee Assistance Program (EAP), company-paid holidays, paid sick leave, and vacation time. We also comply with all applicable laws regarding Paid Family Leave and other leaves of absence.<br>Not ready to apply? Join our Talent Community to get relevant job alerts straight to your inbox.<br><br>At Ciena, we are committed to building and fostering an environment in which our employees feel respected, valued, and heard.  Ciena values the diversity of its workforce and respects its employees as individuals. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination.<br>Ciena is an Equal Opportunity Employer, including disability and protected veteran status.<br>If contacted in relation to a job opportunity, please advise Ciena of any accommodation measures you may require.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Ciena: SVT/PV Engineer 1]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://ciena.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Careers/job/Ottawa/SVT-PV-Engineer-1_R028935?Job_Application_ID=JOB_APPLICATION-3-1150225&Location_Country=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&Location_Country=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&workerSubType=ac99acc6fb6b108fe664fb350ba7ae78&jobFamilyGroup=f08e25a5d78010903df730510aefa016]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>Ottawa<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R028935<br>As the global leader in high-speed connectivity, Ciena is committed to a people-first approach. Our teams enjoy a culture focused on prioritizing a flexible work environment that empowers individual growth, well-being, and belonging. We’re a technology company that leads with our humanity—driving our business priorities alongside meaningful social, community, and societal impact.<br>How You Will Contribute<br>Review system requirements and functional specifications to ensure alignment with project goals.<br>Develop comprehensive test plans and test cases for functional-level software testing.<br>Identify test requirements, configure lab environments, and prepare for test execution.<br>Create Python test scripts using existing automation infrastructure to streamline testing processes.<br>Execute test cases and report results with artifacts using Test Rail to maintain traceability.<br>Collaborate closely with multi-disciplinary teams throughout the software release cycle to ensure compliance and thorough testing.<br>Debug and isolate issues in collaboration with the design team to facilitate quick resolution.<br>Document test results, issues identified, and generate weekly progress and status reports.<br> The Must Haves<br>Bachelor’s degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or equivalent.<br>Knowledge and/or hands-on experience with scripting using Python.<br>Familiarity with traffic generators such as Ixia and/or Spirent Test Centre.<br>Understanding of L2/L3 and Passive Optical Network (PON) technologies.<br>Exposure to troubleshooting and debugging techniques.<br>Some experience in a software testing capacity.<br> Nice to Haves<br>Knowledge and/or hands-on experience in networking (e.g., switches, bridges, TCP/IP configuration, Telnet/SSH, FTP/TFTP).<br>Familiarity with MPLS, Ethernet OAM (Y.1731, 802.1ag), and virtual technologies such as VNF, SDN, and Orchestration.<br>Experience validating customer documentation for accuracy.<br>Exposure to agile development processes and scrum meetings.<br>Understanding of SAOS 10.x program deliverables, including Packet Software and Access organization contributions.<br>Demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively with multi-disciplinary teams, including Development primes and Product Line Architects.<br> Pay Range<br>The salary range for this role in Ottawa is $64,100 - $102,300.<br> Join Ciena’s Routing and Switching Portfolio (RSP), a complete family of products for the access and aggregation tiers of the network, and contribute to delivering Carrier Ethernet solutions that shape the future of connectivity.<br>Pay ranges at Ciena are designed to accommodate variations in knowledge, skills, experience, market conditions, and locations, reflecting our diverse products, industries, and lines of business. Please note that the pay range information provided in this posting pertains specifically to the primary location, which is the top location listed in case multiple locations are available.<br>Non-Sales employees may be eligible for a discretionary incentive bonus, while Sales employees may be eligible for a sales commission. In addition to competitive compensation, Ciena offers a comprehensive benefits package, including medical, dental, and vision plans, participation in 401(K) (USA) & DCPP (Canada) with company matching, Employee Stock Purchase Program (ESPP), Employee Assistance Program (EAP), company-paid holidays, paid sick leave, and vacation time. We also comply with all applicable laws regarding Paid Family Leave and other leaves of absence.<br>Not ready to apply? Join our Talent Community to get relevant job alerts straight to your inbox.<br><br>At Ciena, we are committed to building and fostering an environment in which our employees feel respected, valued, and heard.  Ciena values the diversity of its workforce and respects its employees as individuals. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination.<br>Ciena is an Equal Opportunity Employer, including disability and protected veteran status.<br>If contacted in relation to a job opportunity, please advise Ciena of any accommodation measures you may require.]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>